{
    "t3_1t5b065": {
        "id": "t3_1t5b065",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-06T12:09:47.157Z",
        "title": "Should i boycott Pepsi?",
        "body": "I am looking for an alternative for Coca-Cola and realized that Pepsi isn't on the BDS boycott list, but some people say that we should boycott Pepsi. Does someone know the answer?",
        "keywords": {
            "boycott": 3,
            "pepsi": 3,
            "looking": 1,
            "alternative": 1,
            "realized": 1,
            "bd": 1,
            "list": 1,
            "people": 1,
            "say": 1,
            "answer": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Pepsi",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Coca-Cola",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Pepsi",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "BDS",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Pepsi",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ],
        "last_cached": true
    },
    "t3_1t4yem6": {
        "id": "t3_1t4yem6",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-06T01:14:21.508Z",
        "title": "Booking accomodation for travel",
        "body": "Looking for suggestions on best ways to book accomodation in Europe (France, Poland) without using AirBnB or Booking dot com.\n\nAlso if there are any other key accommodation websites that are boycotted?\n\nThanks!",
        "keywords": {
            "booking": 2,
            "accomodation": 2,
            "travel": 1,
            "looking": 1,
            "suggestion": 1,
            "best": 1,
            "way": 1,
            "book": 1,
            "europe": 1,
            "france": 1,
            "poland": 1,
            "without": 1,
            "using": 1,
            "airbnb": 1,
            "dot": 1,
            "key": 1,
            "accommodation": 1,
            "website": 1,
            "boycotted": 1,
            "thanks": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Europe",
                "label": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "text": "France",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Poland",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t576l0": {
        "id": "t3_1t576l0",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-06T08:50:53.911Z",
        "title": "Disoccupied",
        "body": "Hi folks! I am posting here because I want to know what you think of Disoccupied’s ranking system. I have researched brands that are less than 10% owned in part by Vanguard for example, but other sites like No Thanks cite them as boycotted, but disoccupied has this system.\n\nWhat do you guys think?",
        "keywords": {
            "disoccupied": 3,
            "hi": 1,
            "folk": 1,
            "posting": 1,
            "think": 2,
            "ranking": 1,
            "system": 2,
            "researched": 1,
            "brand": 1,
            "less": 1,
            "10": 1,
            "owned": 1,
            "part": 1,
            "vanguard": 1,
            "example": 1,
            "site": 1,
            "thanks": 1,
            "cite": 1,
            "boycotted": 1,
            "guy": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Disoccupied",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "less than 10%",
                "label": "PERCENT"
            },
            {
                "text": "Vanguard",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t4s0kt": {
        "id": "t3_1t4s0kt",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T20:49:50.611Z",
        "title": "Is Jellycat a boycott-safe company?",
        "body": "I was thinking about buying a Jellycat for fidgeting (Sky Dragon) but I wanted to also make sure that Jellycat does not support Israel or have any connections. Should I buy a Jellycat? Is it safe?",
        "keywords": {
            "jellycat": 4,
            "company": 1,
            "thinking": 1,
            "buying": 1,
            "fidgeting": 1,
            "sky": 1,
            "dragon": 1,
            "sure": 1,
            "support": 1,
            "israel": 1,
            "connection": 1,
            "buy": 1,
            "safe": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Sky Dragon",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Jellycat",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t4rehf": {
        "id": "t3_1t4rehf",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T20:27:20.096Z",
        "title": "Is it safe to watch a 3D movie which had animated with a problematic software",
        "body": "I was thinking about watching the TADC: The Last Act movie when it comes out and I wanted to know if it was okay for me to watch and enjoy it even though Glitch Productions used a problematic animation software. Please help cause I am super paranoid right now! Thanks!",
        "keywords": {
            "safe": 1,
            "watch": 2,
            "3d": 1,
            "movie": 2,
            "animated": 1,
            "problematic": 2,
            "software": 2,
            "thinking": 1,
            "watching": 1,
            "tadc": 1,
            "last": 1,
            "act": 1,
            "come": 1,
            "okay": 1,
            "enjoy": 1,
            "though": 1,
            "glitch": 1,
            "production": 1,
            "used": 1,
            "animation": 1,
            "please": 1,
            "help": 1,
            "cause": 1,
            "super": 1,
            "paranoid": 1,
            "right": 1,
            "thanks": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Glitch Productions",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t460qx": {
        "id": "t3_1t460qx",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T05:16:54.203Z",
        "title": "Graphic Novels by Palestinians",
        "body": "",
        "keywords": {
            "graphic": 1,
            "novel": 1,
            "palestinian": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Graphic Novels",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Palestinians",
                "label": "NORP"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t3h9uw": {
        "id": "t3_1t3h9uw",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-04T13:10:05.660Z",
        "title": "Do companies still benefit if you use a birthday coupon for a free gift? would it go against bds?",
        "body": "So I got a birthday coupon from a place I personally boycott and one on the bds list. should i use it and unsubscribe for the future?",
        "keywords": {
            "company": 1,
            "benefit": 1,
            "use": 2,
            "birthday": 2,
            "coupon": 2,
            "free": 1,
            "gift": 1,
            "bd": 2,
            "place": 1,
            "personally": 1,
            "boycott": 1,
            "one": 1,
            "list": 1,
            "unsubscribe": 1,
            "future": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "bds",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t3fd4w": {
        "id": "t3_1t3fd4w",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-04T11:49:38.666Z",
        "title": "Iran says it turns back US warship from Strait of Hormuz, according to their news Agency.",
        "body": "",
        "keywords": {
            "iran": 1,
            "say": 1,
            "turn": 1,
            "back": 1,
            "warship": 1,
            "strait": 1,
            "hormuz": 1,
            "according": 1,
            "news": 1,
            "agency": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Iran",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "US",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Strait of Hormuz",
                "label": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "text": "Agency",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t4cf6k": {
        "id": "t3_1t4cf6k",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T11:17:15.449Z",
        "title": "Hair dye alternatives",
        "body": "Hey\n\nI was wondering whether there was a cheap hair dye alternatives in norway. I used to dye my own hair using Garnier or Schwarzkopf. I am looking for something with red shades, something that could perhaps be found in stores, and something that won't break my bank account.\n\nThanks in advance",
        "keywords": {
            "hair": 3,
            "dye": 3,
            "alternative": 2,
            "hey": 1,
            "wondering": 1,
            "whether": 1,
            "cheap": 1,
            "norway": 1,
            "used": 1,
            "using": 1,
            "garnier": 1,
            "schwarzkopf": 1,
            "looking": 1,
            "something": 3,
            "red": 1,
            "shade": 1,
            "perhaps": 1,
            "found": 1,
            "store": 1,
            "wo": 1,
            "break": 1,
            "bank": 1,
            "account": 1,
            "thanks": 1,
            "advance": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "norway",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Garnier",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Schwarzkopf",
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t2n2pk": {
        "id": "t3_1t2n2pk",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-03T14:33:15.374Z",
        "title": "Boycott safe e-book websites?",
        "body": "I don’t wanna get pirated content since I value creators’ work and it’s haram. Either way where can I buy e-books? Amazon and Kobo are both boycotted.\n\nAlso, feel free to list any authors that you know are pro-zionism. For me and others to be wary. I know that Jordan Peterson is a zionist.\n\nEdit: Many typos, I wrote it in a rush.",
        "keywords": {
            "boycott": 1,
            "safe": 1,
            "website": 1,
            "wan": 1,
            "na": 1,
            "pirated": 1,
            "content": 1,
            "since": 1,
            "value": 1,
            "creator": 1,
            "work": 1,
            "haram": 1,
            "either": 1,
            "way": 1,
            "buy": 1,
            "amazon": 1,
            "kobo": 1,
            "boycotted": 1,
            "feel": 1,
            "free": 1,
            "list": 1,
            "author": 1,
            "others": 1,
            "wary": 1,
            "jordan": 1,
            "peterson": 1,
            "zionist": 1,
            "typo": 1,
            "wrote": 1,
            "rush": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Boycott",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Amazon",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Kobo",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Jordan Peterson",
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t2tqiw": {
        "id": "t3_1t2tqiw",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-03T18:42:39.770Z",
        "title": "Where are we buying fruit and veg from (UK)?",
        "body": "So I was exclusively buying from Aldi since Asda was put on the boycott list. Just discovered Aldi's primary fruit and veg supplier is now on the No Thanks list. The only other major supermarket I know is safe is Co-op, and even if we had one nearby, I can't afford that kind of money regularly.\n\nWhere are you guys getting fruit and veg? There're no local suppliers near me. Do I just have to bite the bullet on this one?",
        "keywords": {
            "buying": 2,
            "fruit": 3,
            "veg": 3,
            "uk": 1,
            "exclusively": 1,
            "aldi": 2,
            "since": 1,
            "asda": 1,
            "put": 1,
            "boycott": 1,
            "list": 2,
            "discovered": 1,
            "primary": 1,
            "supplier": 2,
            "thanks": 1,
            "major": 1,
            "supermarket": 1,
            "safe": 1,
            "one": 2,
            "nearby": 1,
            "ca": 1,
            "afford": 1,
            "kind": 1,
            "money": 1,
            "regularly": 1,
            "guy": 1,
            "local": 1,
            "near": 1,
            "bite": 1,
            "bullet": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "UK",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Aldi",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Asda",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Aldi",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t2jcv3": {
        "id": "t3_1t2jcv3",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-03T11:51:48.188Z",
        "title": "Israel boycott",
        "body": "Hey can someone confirm that is keune shampoo on boycott list in 2026 or not google is being sceptical",
        "keywords": {
            "israel": 1,
            "boycott": 2,
            "hey": 1,
            "confirm": 1,
            "keune": 1,
            "shampoo": 1,
            "list": 1,
            "2026": 1,
            "google": 1,
            "sceptical": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "2026",
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t35jqw": {
        "id": "t3_1t35jqw",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-04T02:55:06.431Z",
        "title": "Alternative Haircare for Dry/Frizzy Curly Hair? (Herbal Essences)",
        "body": "Hi folks!\n\nI’m from Canada and have been trying to find alternatives to my Herbal Essences conditioner for a while now after learning they are invested in Israel. My hair is super dry, between 2C and 3B depending on the season, and gets weighed down by heavy products. A light leave-in conditioner would be great to find too. Right now I’ve just been using coconut oil, but it makes my hair super greasy if I use it too often, and it doesn’t do much to define my curls.\n\nThank you all so much in advance for the help! <3",
        "keywords": {
            "alternative": 2,
            "haircare": 1,
            "curly": 1,
            "hair": 3,
            "herbal": 2,
            "essence": 2,
            "hi": 1,
            "folk": 1,
            "canada": 1,
            "trying": 1,
            "find": 2,
            "conditioner": 2,
            "learning": 1,
            "invested": 1,
            "israel": 1,
            "super": 2,
            "dry": 1,
            "2c": 1,
            "3b": 1,
            "depending": 1,
            "season": 1,
            "get": 1,
            "weighed": 1,
            "heavy": 1,
            "product": 1,
            "light": 1,
            "great": 1,
            "right": 1,
            "using": 1,
            "coconut": 1,
            "oil": 1,
            "make": 1,
            "greasy": 1,
            "use": 1,
            "often": 1,
            "define": 1,
            "curl": 1,
            "thank": 1,
            "advance": 1,
            "help": 1,
            "3": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Dry/Frizzy Curly Hair",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Herbal Essences",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Canada",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Herbal Essences",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "2C",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "3B",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "the season",
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t1k2ce": {
        "id": "t3_1t1k2ce",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-02T08:25:24.058Z",
        "title": "Born during Israel’s genocide: Gaza’s child survivors bear the scars of war",
        "body": "",
        "keywords": {
            "born": 1,
            "israel": 1,
            "genocide": 1,
            "gaza": 1,
            "child": 1,
            "survivor": 1,
            "bear": 1,
            "scar": 1,
            "war": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Gaza",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t1mu7k": {
        "id": "t3_1t1mu7k",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-02T11:03:03.642Z",
        "title": "Edible locusts not from Occupied Palestine?",
        "body": "I know this is kinda a wild ask but I’ve been wanting to try incorporating locusts in my diet for a good form of protein, but a lot of edible locusts on the market are farmed in Occupied Palestine. I’ve found a few brands that claim to be either Thai or Chinese but don’t have their farm location disclosed so I’m distrusting. If anyone knows of a good brand where I can try them without suppprting apartheid I’d appreciate it!",
        "keywords": {
            "edible": 2,
            "locust": 3,
            "occupied": 2,
            "palestine": 2,
            "kinda": 1,
            "wild": 1,
            "ask": 1,
            "wanting": 1,
            "try": 2,
            "incorporating": 1,
            "diet": 1,
            "good": 2,
            "form": 1,
            "protein": 1,
            "market": 1,
            "farmed": 1,
            "found": 1,
            "brand": 2,
            "claim": 1,
            "either": 1,
            "thai": 1,
            "chinese": 1,
            "farm": 1,
            "location": 1,
            "disclosed": 1,
            "distrusting": 1,
            "without": 1,
            "suppprting": 1,
            "apartheid": 1,
            "appreciate": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Palestine",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Palestine",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Thai",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Chinese",
                "label": "NORP"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t2hk75": {
        "id": "t3_1t2hk75",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-03T10:14:52.940Z",
        "title": "Alternatives to Aussie 3 minute miracle conditioner",
        "body": "I used to use Aussie 3 minute miracle reconstructer conditioner, and I've been looking for ages and nothing seems to work quite as well. Palmer's and Monday conditioners seem to work okay (Monday more than Palmer's), but wondering if anyone's aware of any good alternatives, ideally ones that are leave-in but not ones that you apply when the hair is damp & don't wash off, nor ones where you leave it in for several minutes and then wash off but washing it off requires cold water.",
        "keywords": {
            "alternative": 2,
            "aussie": 2,
            "3": 2,
            "minute": 3,
            "miracle": 2,
            "conditioner": 3,
            "used": 1,
            "use": 1,
            "reconstructer": 1,
            "looking": 1,
            "age": 1,
            "nothing": 1,
            "seems": 1,
            "work": 2,
            "well": 1,
            "palmer": 2,
            "monday": 2,
            "seem": 1,
            "okay": 1,
            "wondering": 1,
            "aware": 1,
            "good": 1,
            "ideally": 1,
            "one": 3,
            "apply": 1,
            "hair": 1,
            "damp": 1,
            "wash": 2,
            "leave": 1,
            "several": 1,
            "washing": 1,
            "requires": 1,
            "cold": 1,
            "water": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Aussie 3 minute miracle",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "3 minute",
                "label": "TIME"
            },
            {
                "text": "Monday",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Monday",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "several minutes",
                "label": "TIME"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t0z73j": {
        "id": "t3_1t0z73j",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-01T16:59:51.247Z",
        "title": "How AI *should* answer questions about israel but never does",
        "body": "Probably the first honest answer I've seen from any AI platform...\n\nGOOD ON THEM!!!\n\nEdit: I want to add that I'm not some pro-AI stan. But chances are you know someone using AI and I urge you to point people towards platforms that are willing to be (RIGHTFULLY) critical of Israel. ChatGPT and Claude combined have something like 1b users being told \"The situation between Israel and Gaza is complicated\" and whatever other BS response.",
        "keywords": {
            "ai": 3,
            "answer": 2,
            "question": 1,
            "israel": 3,
            "never": 1,
            "first": 1,
            "honest": 1,
            "seen": 1,
            "platform": 2,
            "good": 1,
            "add": 1,
            "stan": 1,
            "chance": 1,
            "using": 1,
            "urge": 1,
            "point": 1,
            "people": 1,
            "towards": 1,
            "willing": 1,
            "rightfully": 1,
            "critical": 1,
            "chatgpt": 1,
            "claude": 1,
            "combined": 1,
            "something": 1,
            "1b": 1,
            "user": 1,
            "told": 1,
            "situation": 1,
            "gaza": 1,
            "complicated": 1,
            "whatever": 1,
            "b": 1,
            "response": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "first",
                "label": "ORDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "AI",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "AI",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "RIGHTFULLY",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Claude",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "1b",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Gaza",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t0y5mg": {
        "id": "t3_1t0y5mg",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-01T16:22:02.508Z",
        "title": "Duck Duck Go",
        "body": "The search engine Duck Duck Go comes up as green on No Thanks. But asking questions of its duck.ai version of Grok or Chat GPT reveals a clear pro Israel bias. I tried to ask it questions about the recent Golders Green stabbing in London. The media are going with an anti-Semitic narrative, which would be fair enough if that were the actual motive. They’re using it as an excuse to condemn the Genocide Protests in London as antisemitism. So I asked duck.ai how many victims there were, and it was able to name two Jewish victims, one aged 76 and one aged 34. It found its info from the Times of Israel and the BBC. Both Zionist news institutions. I probed duck.ai further because I happen to know, from the Crown Prosecution Website, that the same suspect is charged with not two but three victims, one of whom is a Muslim, although the CPS don’t actually name any of the victims or state a motive. The duck.ai first denied all knowledge of victim 3, then tried to paint the third person as a suspect, then it renamed the Muslim guy as a Jewish person. So it goes to show, the Zionists can get their teeth into any software, “Good For Now” or not.",
        "keywords": {
            "duck": 4,
            "search": 1,
            "engine": 1,
            "come": 1,
            "green": 2,
            "thanks": 1,
            "asking": 1,
            "question": 2,
            "version": 1,
            "grok": 1,
            "chat": 1,
            "gpt": 1,
            "reveals": 1,
            "clear": 1,
            "pro": 1,
            "israel": 2,
            "bias": 1,
            "tried": 2,
            "ask": 1,
            "recent": 1,
            "golders": 1,
            "stabbing": 1,
            "london": 2,
            "medium": 1,
            "going": 1,
            "narrative": 1,
            "fair": 1,
            "enough": 1,
            "actual": 1,
            "motive": 2,
            "using": 1,
            "excuse": 1,
            "condemn": 1,
            "genocide": 1,
            "protest": 1,
            "antisemitism": 1,
            "asked": 1,
            "victim": 5,
            "able": 1,
            "name": 2,
            "two": 2,
            "jewish": 2,
            "one": 3,
            "aged": 2,
            "76": 1,
            "found": 1,
            "info": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "bbc": 1,
            "zionist": 2,
            "news": 1,
            "institution": 1,
            "probed": 1,
            "happen": 1,
            "crown": 1,
            "prosecution": 1,
            "website": 1,
            "suspect": 2,
            "charged": 1,
            "three": 1,
            "muslim": 2,
            "although": 1,
            "cps": 1,
            "state": 1,
            "first": 1,
            "denied": 1,
            "knowledge": 1,
            "3": 1,
            "paint": 1,
            "third": 1,
            "person": 2,
            "renamed": 1,
            "guy": 1,
            "show": 1,
            "teeth": 1,
            "software": 1,
            "good": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Duck Duck",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Grok",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Chat GPT",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Golders Green",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "London",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "the Genocide Protests",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
            },
            {
                "text": "London",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "two",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Jewish",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "one",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "76",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "one",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "34",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "the Times of Israel",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "BBC",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Zionist",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "the Crown Prosecution Website",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "two",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "three",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "one",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Muslim",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "CPS",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "3",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "third",
                "label": "ORDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Muslim",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Jewish",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Zionists",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Good For Now",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t15jjy": {
        "id": "t3_1t15jjy",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-01T20:50:04.532Z",
        "title": "make it make sense 🤔",
        "body": "I'm vegan and I was asking a vegan forum for good vegan ice cream suggestions. I couldn't find much. Some people suggested I get the non dairy Ben & Jerry's flavors. I said I won't be buying Ben & Jerry's because I have boycotted them a long time ago. suddenly, everyone attacked me.\n\nSo, am I the only vegan person who also is boycotting isreal? No one I know who boycotted Isreal is vegan, and none of the other vegans in these spaces are boycotting Isreal.\n\nI find it extremely hypnotical to pick and choose whether to boycott human genocide vs animal genocide. why not boycott both?\n\nAny other vegans here?",
        "keywords": {
            "sense": 1,
            "vegan": 7,
            "asking": 1,
            "forum": 1,
            "good": 1,
            "ice": 1,
            "cream": 1,
            "suggestion": 1,
            "find": 2,
            "people": 1,
            "suggested": 1,
            "non": 1,
            "dairy": 1,
            "ben": 2,
            "jerry": 2,
            "flavor": 1,
            "said": 1,
            "wo": 1,
            "buying": 1,
            "boycotted": 2,
            "long": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "ago": 1,
            "suddenly": 1,
            "everyone": 1,
            "attacked": 1,
            "person": 1,
            "boycotting": 2,
            "isreal": 3,
            "one": 1,
            "none": 1,
            "space": 1,
            "extremely": 1,
            "hypnotical": 1,
            "pick": 1,
            "choose": 1,
            "whether": 1,
            "boycott": 2,
            "human": 1,
            "genocide": 2,
            "v": 1,
            "animal": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "🤔",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Ben & Jerry's",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Isreal",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Isreal",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t0op1m": {
        "id": "t3_1t0op1m",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-01T09:41:43.475Z",
        "title": "Are the following movies okay to watch? They came out recently.",
        "body": "Animal Farm\n\nMicheal\n\nThe Super Mario Galaxy Movie",
        "keywords": {
            "following": 1,
            "movie": 2,
            "okay": 1,
            "watch": 1,
            "came": 1,
            "recently": 1,
            "animal": 1,
            "farm": 1,
            "micheal": 1,
            "super": 1,
            "mario": 1,
            "galaxy": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Animal Farm\n\nMicheal\n\nThe Super Mario Galaxy Movie",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t0idef": {
        "id": "t3_1t0idef",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-01T03:55:05.271Z",
        "title": "What kind of chocolate can I buy in Europe that doesn't support genocide ?",
        "body": "Am more into dark chocolate, but any kind of suggestions is good,",
        "keywords": {
            "kind": 2,
            "chocolate": 2,
            "buy": 1,
            "europe": 1,
            "support": 1,
            "genocide": 1,
            "dark": 1,
            "suggestion": 1,
            "good": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Europe",
                "label": "LOC"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t0r9sc": {
        "id": "t3_1t0r9sc",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-01T11:54:34.464Z",
        "title": "Non USA and ProIsrael peripherics please!",
        "body": "Im looking for a vertical mouse from some brand that isnt from the USA (sorry for any USA members, is nothing against you, is againts your goverment) and that doesnt support Israhell, and i cant really find anything that has good reviews. Thank you very much in advance <3\nPS: Im based in Spain!",
        "keywords": {
            "non": 1,
            "usa": 3,
            "proisrael": 1,
            "peripherics": 1,
            "please": 1,
            "im": 2,
            "looking": 1,
            "vertical": 1,
            "mouse": 1,
            "brand": 1,
            "isnt": 1,
            "sorry": 1,
            "member": 1,
            "nothing": 1,
            "againts": 1,
            "goverment": 1,
            "doesnt": 1,
            "support": 1,
            "israhell": 1,
            "cant": 1,
            "find": 1,
            "anything": 1,
            "good": 1,
            "review": 1,
            "thank": 1,
            "advance": 1,
            "3": 1,
            "p": 1,
            "based": 1,
            "spain": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Non USA",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "ProIsrael",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "USA",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "USA",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israhell",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Spain",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1szxqvw": {
        "id": "t3_1szxqvw",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-30T14:30:53.223Z",
        "title": "Non-Zionist Yoga Brand",
        "body": "Sorry for the low effort post. I'm looking to purchase a yoga / athlesuire brand gift card but I want to avoid any zio linked trash. Obviously shit like Alo, and Lululemon is out. Checking to see if anyone knows any brands off hand that would be good. Gymshark comes to mind, but curious if anyone has some good ideas.",
        "keywords": {
            "yoga": 2,
            "brand": 3,
            "sorry": 1,
            "low": 1,
            "effort": 1,
            "looking": 1,
            "purchase": 1,
            "athlesuire": 1,
            "gift": 1,
            "card": 1,
            "avoid": 1,
            "zio": 1,
            "linked": 1,
            "trash": 1,
            "obviously": 1,
            "shit": 1,
            "alo": 1,
            "lululemon": 1,
            "checking": 1,
            "see": 1,
            "hand": 1,
            "good": 2,
            "gymshark": 1,
            "come": 1,
            "mind": 1,
            "curious": 1,
            "idea": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Non-Zionist Yoga Brand",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Alo",
                "label": "PRODUCT"
            },
            {
                "text": "Lululemon",
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1sxkpsw": {
        "id": "t3_1sxkpsw",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-27T23:42:54.837Z",
        "title": "Inexpensive Clothing Brands",
        "body": "I am looking for brands that sell basic clothing items (like plain t-shirts, shorts, pants, socks, underwear) that are inexpensive, if possible. It seems like every major clothing brand is connected to Israel, and I have only seen a few alternatives listed on sites like Disoccupied, most of which seem to be on the more expensive side.\n\nThe two brands that seemed like possibilities that were listed as safe alternatives by Disoccupied were Honest Basics and Pact, but it seems that Honest Basics does not ship to the US anymore, and I saw comments saying that Pact has inconsistent quality. I know that thrifting is usually the safest option, but some clothing items I would only want to buy new for the sake of hygiene.\n\nDoes anyone have any suggestions?\n\nThank you!",
        "keywords": {
            "inexpensive": 2,
            "clothing": 4,
            "brand": 4,
            "looking": 1,
            "sell": 1,
            "basic": 3,
            "item": 2,
            "plain": 1,
            "short": 1,
            "pant": 1,
            "sock": 1,
            "underwear": 1,
            "possible": 1,
            "seems": 2,
            "every": 1,
            "major": 1,
            "connected": 1,
            "israel": 1,
            "seen": 1,
            "alternative": 2,
            "listed": 2,
            "site": 1,
            "disoccupied": 2,
            "seem": 1,
            "expensive": 1,
            "side": 1,
            "two": 1,
            "seemed": 1,
            "possibility": 1,
            "safe": 1,
            "honest": 2,
            "pact": 2,
            "ship": 1,
            "anymore": 1,
            "saw": 1,
            "saying": 1,
            "inconsistent": 1,
            "quality": 1,
            "thrifting": 1,
            "usually": 1,
            "safest": 1,
            "option": 1,
            "buy": 1,
            "new": 1,
            "sake": 1,
            "hygiene": 1,
            "suggestion": 1,
            "thank": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Disoccupied",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "two",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Disoccupied",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Honest Basics and Pact",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Honest Basics",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "US",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1sytlr7": {
        "id": "t3_1sytlr7",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-29T09:17:28.050Z",
        "title": "I found this wallpaper on another subreddit so i wanted to share it with everyone here.",
        "body": "Credit to u/Lenoxx97",
        "keywords": {
            "found": 1,
            "wallpaper": 1,
            "another": 1,
            "share": 1,
            "everyone": 1,
            "credit": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": []
    },
    "t3_1sz8s39": {
        "id": "t3_1sz8s39",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-29T19:20:43.824Z",
        "title": "Microsoft removes Israeli names for occupied West Bank",
        "body": "The primary group that pressured Microsoft to change the labels on Bing Maps is the Arab Center for the Advancement of Social Media, also known as 7amleh\n\nActivism Matters",
        "keywords": {
            "microsoft": 2,
            "remove": 1,
            "israeli": 1,
            "name": 1,
            "occupied": 1,
            "west": 1,
            "bank": 1,
            "primary": 1,
            "group": 1,
            "pressured": 1,
            "change": 1,
            "label": 1,
            "bing": 1,
            "map": 1,
            "arab": 1,
            "center": 1,
            "advancement": 1,
            "social": 1,
            "medium": 1,
            "known": 1,
            "7amleh": 1,
            "activism": 1,
            "matter": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Microsoft",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israeli",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "West Bank",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Microsoft",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Bing Maps",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "the Arab Center",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "the Advancement of Social Media",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1sw4zw1": {
        "id": "t3_1sw4zw1",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-26T11:25:48.448Z",
        "title": "Alternatives to NYX cosmetics that are cruelty free, and vegan and available in Denmark",
        "body": "Hey Reddit i found out my favorite makeup brand is sadly on the boycott list. The issue is that a lot of the brands that is not on the list is sadly not vegan and cruelty free.\n\nI know about essence and Catrice which is not on the list and is also cruelty free but I need some other good recommendations for brands that are cruelty free and cheap.\n\nIt is very important for me to only support ethical brands because I am a punk/alternative person and also vegetarian trying to be vegan",
        "keywords": {
            "alternative": 1,
            "nyx": 1,
            "cosmetic": 1,
            "cruelty": 4,
            "free": 4,
            "vegan": 3,
            "available": 1,
            "denmark": 1,
            "hey": 1,
            "found": 1,
            "favorite": 1,
            "makeup": 1,
            "brand": 4,
            "sadly": 2,
            "boycott": 1,
            "list": 3,
            "issue": 1,
            "essence": 1,
            "catrice": 1,
            "need": 1,
            "good": 1,
            "recommendation": 1,
            "cheap": 1,
            "important": 1,
            "support": 1,
            "ethical": 1,
            "person": 1,
            "vegetarian": 1,
            "trying": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "NYX",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Denmark",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Catrice",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1suw294": {
        "id": "t3_1suw294",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-24T23:43:03.720Z",
        "title": "Catherine O'Neill Thorn (@caitoneill)",
        "body": "Yup. It’s pretty judgey, I realise that. It’s all most of us can do while a million men, women and children are losing their precious lives in horrific ways. Surely we can break our addiction to the extraction machine that is using our money to slaughter hundreds of thousands of people.",
        "keywords": {
            "catherine": 1,
            "thorn": 1,
            "caitoneill": 1,
            "yup": 1,
            "pretty": 1,
            "judgey": 1,
            "realise": 1,
            "million": 1,
            "men": 1,
            "woman": 1,
            "child": 1,
            "losing": 1,
            "precious": 1,
            "life": 1,
            "horrific": 1,
            "way": 1,
            "surely": 1,
            "break": 1,
            "addiction": 1,
            "extraction": 1,
            "machine": 1,
            "using": 1,
            "money": 1,
            "slaughter": 1,
            "hundred": 1,
            "thousand": 1,
            "people": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Catherine O'Neill Thorn",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "million",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "hundreds of thousands",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1sur7ud": {
        "id": "t3_1sur7ud",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-24T20:27:42.499Z",
        "title": "I mean my generation lost faith in Wikipedia so long ago even for trivial informations, but I think this post may be of help for ppl who are unaware",
        "body": "",
        "keywords": {
            "mean": 1,
            "generation": 1,
            "lost": 1,
            "faith": 1,
            "wikipedia": 1,
            "long": 1,
            "ago": 1,
            "trivial": 1,
            "information": 1,
            "think": 1,
            "help": 1,
            "ppl": 1,
            "unaware": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Wikipedia",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1svo5s1": {
        "id": "t3_1svo5s1",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-25T21:14:11.390Z",
        "title": "Is Jessica Simpson brand on the boycott list? Parent company is With You Inc",
        "body": "I tried to look online but I couldn’t find anything about it, wanted to know if it’s ok to buy this brand. I couldn’t find anything about her stance either",
        "keywords": {
            "jessica": 1,
            "simpson": 1,
            "brand": 2,
            "boycott": 1,
            "list": 1,
            "parent": 1,
            "company": 1,
            "inc": 1,
            "tried": 1,
            "online": 1,
            "find": 2,
            "anything": 2,
            "ok": 1,
            "buy": 1,
            "stance": 1,
            "either": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Jessica Simpson",
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1ssu0tz": {
        "id": "t3_1ssu0tz",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-22T18:31:02.798Z",
        "title": "Are these dates really from Jordan?",
        "body": "I came across these Medjool dates at Lidl in Belgium. I was wondering if they really were from Jordan as they claim on the label or it is 'date laundering' as I've read it called in order to hide their Israeli origin and sell.\n\nThank you",
        "keywords": {
            "date": 2,
            "jordan": 2,
            "came": 1,
            "across": 1,
            "medjool": 1,
            "lidl": 1,
            "belgium": 1,
            "wondering": 1,
            "claim": 1,
            "label": 1,
            "laundering": 1,
            "read": 1,
            "called": 1,
            "order": 1,
            "hide": 1,
            "israeli": 1,
            "origin": 1,
            "sell": 1,
            "thank": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Jordan",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Lidl",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Belgium",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Jordan",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israeli",
                "label": "NORP"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1stp4g0": {
        "id": "t3_1stp4g0",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-23T17:18:04.853Z",
        "title": "It's hilarious how Israel is doing the same thing they say the Nazis did",
        "body": "I always watched these shows or movies that showed how vile the Nazis were, but Israel is doing worse things and nobody is doing anything to stop it.",
        "keywords": {
            "hilarious": 1,
            "israel": 2,
            "say": 1,
            "nazi": 2,
            "always": 1,
            "watched": 1,
            "show": 1,
            "movie": 1,
            "showed": 1,
            "vile": 1,
            "worse": 1,
            "nobody": 1,
            "anything": 1,
            "stop": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Nazis",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Nazis",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1sumb7b": {
        "id": "t3_1sumb7b",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-24T17:27:40.527Z",
        "title": "I think takis might be on the boycott list",
        "body": "So for explanation, the parent company of takis is Grupo bimbo and they invested in an Israeli food tech company. I'm unsure and I did some research.\n\nSource:\n\nhttps://disoccupied.com/brand/takis\n\nhttps://israelproducts.cloud/does-takis-support-israel/",
        "keywords": {
            "think": 1,
            "takis": 2,
            "boycott": 1,
            "list": 1,
            "explanation": 1,
            "parent": 1,
            "company": 2,
            "grupo": 1,
            "bimbo": 1,
            "invested": 1,
            "israeli": 1,
            "food": 1,
            "tech": 1,
            "unsure": 1,
            "research": 1,
            "source": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Grupo",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israeli",
                "label": "NORP"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1srtzw5": {
        "id": "t3_1srtzw5",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-21T17:09:27.042Z",
        "title": "Credit Unions",
        "body": "I’m looking to switch from Scotiabank due to their ties with Israel and being on BDS.\n\nThe credit union I’m joining was originally established by the Lithuanian community - when I looked it up, it appears that Lithuania is supportive of Israel (please correct me if I’m wrong).\n\nI’m worried joining this CU may also supoort/fund Israel’s genocide. Should I just check the CU’s funding/investment history as laid out online, and if there are no ties to Israel stated, do you think it’s okay to open an account? I just don’t want to go from one complicit institution to another.\n\nThank you!",
        "keywords": {
            "credit": 2,
            "union": 2,
            "looking": 1,
            "switch": 1,
            "scotiabank": 1,
            "due": 1,
            "tie": 2,
            "israel": 4,
            "bd": 1,
            "joining": 2,
            "originally": 1,
            "established": 1,
            "lithuanian": 1,
            "community": 1,
            "looked": 1,
            "appears": 1,
            "lithuania": 1,
            "supportive": 1,
            "please": 1,
            "correct": 1,
            "wrong": 1,
            "worried": 1,
            "cu": 2,
            "genocide": 1,
            "check": 1,
            "history": 1,
            "laid": 1,
            "online": 1,
            "stated": 1,
            "think": 1,
            "okay": 1,
            "open": 1,
            "account": 1,
            "one": 1,
            "complicit": 1,
            "institution": 1,
            "another": 1,
            "thank": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Scotiabank",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "BDS",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Lithuanian",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Lithuania",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "CU",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "CU",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "one",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1srvxgu": {
        "id": "t3_1srvxgu",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-21T18:14:14.709Z",
        "title": "Ethical shoe brands/ stores not on the boycott list",
        "body": "Hello! So i live in Germany and i need urgently a new pair of shoes (i moved here during the winter and i don't have any shoes for warmer weather). I tried going to thrift stores but it's a bit challenging cause the choices are extremely limited and the prices are quite high and i feel like every brand of clothing/ shoes is on the boycott list.\n\nIf you have any suggestions, please help\n\nThank you all",
        "keywords": {
            "ethical": 1,
            "shoe": 4,
            "store": 2,
            "boycott": 2,
            "list": 2,
            "hello": 1,
            "live": 1,
            "germany": 1,
            "need": 1,
            "urgently": 1,
            "new": 1,
            "pair": 1,
            "moved": 1,
            "winter": 1,
            "warmer": 1,
            "weather": 1,
            "tried": 1,
            "going": 1,
            "thrift": 1,
            "bit": 1,
            "challenging": 1,
            "cause": 1,
            "choice": 1,
            "extremely": 1,
            "limited": 1,
            "price": 1,
            "high": 1,
            "feel": 1,
            "every": 1,
            "brand": 1,
            "suggestion": 1,
            "please": 1,
            "help": 1,
            "thank": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Germany",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "the winter",
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1ssebu8": {
        "id": "t3_1ssebu8",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-22T07:24:07.653Z",
        "title": "Is United Colours of Benetton safe?",
        "body": "I remember they used to be on some lists, but can't find any info now. Would like to confirm before I go ahead with my purchase.",
        "keywords": {
            "united": 1,
            "colour": 1,
            "benetton": 1,
            "safe": 1,
            "remember": 1,
            "used": 1,
            "list": 1,
            "ca": 1,
            "find": 1,
            "info": 1,
            "confirm": 1,
            "ahead": 1,
            "purchase": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Benetton",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1sqpw84": {
        "id": "t3_1sqpw84",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-20T13:49:06.303Z",
        "title": "The difficult question about computer processors",
        "body": "I would like to ask this community because I got a really helpful answer here before.\n\nLet’s talk computers, phones. Anything that needs a CPU, computer processing unit.\n\nDisclaimer, my technical and political knowledge is not 100%, open to corrections.\n\nAll the information below is alleged to the best of my memory.\n\nIntel. AMD. I’ve looked into the big names. All addicted to military.\n\nNew RISC-V processors. Mostly developed by Chinese companies where the Chinese government had a majority shareholder stake. Problematic because of Ughyur people, Taiwan, Tibet.\n\nThere’s Sifive, but that’s partially owned by Intel. So still problematic.\n\nIndependent processors like Raspberry Pi. But they use Broadcom. Problematic.\n\nI found Japanese brand Renesas. But they use ARM chips. ARM is used in a lot of military im guessing in enterprise deals.\n\nI know the complication. Having the finances and resources to develop this technology even in a small scale is very very expensive.\n\nIs there anyone out there developing medium to fast pace processors that have an ethical supply chain?\n\nAny insights anyone?",
        "keywords": {
            "difficult": 1,
            "question": 1,
            "computer": 3,
            "processor": 4,
            "ask": 1,
            "community": 1,
            "helpful": 1,
            "answer": 1,
            "let": 1,
            "talk": 1,
            "phone": 1,
            "anything": 1,
            "need": 1,
            "cpu": 1,
            "processing": 1,
            "unit": 1,
            "disclaimer": 1,
            "technical": 1,
            "political": 1,
            "knowledge": 1,
            "100": 1,
            "open": 1,
            "correction": 1,
            "information": 1,
            "alleged": 1,
            "best": 1,
            "memory": 1,
            "intel": 2,
            "amd": 1,
            "looked": 1,
            "big": 1,
            "name": 1,
            "addicted": 1,
            "military": 2,
            "new": 1,
            "mostly": 1,
            "developed": 1,
            "chinese": 2,
            "company": 1,
            "government": 1,
            "majority": 1,
            "shareholder": 1,
            "stake": 1,
            "problematic": 3,
            "ughyur": 1,
            "people": 1,
            "taiwan": 1,
            "tibet": 1,
            "sifive": 1,
            "partially": 1,
            "owned": 1,
            "independent": 1,
            "raspberry": 1,
            "pi": 1,
            "use": 2,
            "broadcom": 1,
            "found": 1,
            "japanese": 1,
            "brand": 1,
            "renesas": 1,
            "arm": 2,
            "chip": 1,
            "used": 1,
            "im": 1,
            "guessing": 1,
            "enterprise": 1,
            "deal": 1,
            "complication": 1,
            "finance": 1,
            "resource": 1,
            "develop": 1,
            "technology": 1,
            "small": 1,
            "scale": 1,
            "expensive": 1,
            "developing": 1,
            "medium": 1,
            "fast": 1,
            "pace": 1,
            "ethical": 1,
            "supply": 1,
            "chain": 1,
            "insight": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "CPU",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "100%",
                "label": "PERCENT"
            },
            {
                "text": "Intel",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "AMD",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Chinese",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Chinese",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Ughyur",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Taiwan",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Tibet",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Intel",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Raspberry Pi",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Broadcom.",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
            },
            {
                "text": "Japanese",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Renesas",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1sqajh1": {
        "id": "t3_1sqajh1",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-20T00:57:09.454Z",
        "title": "Protonmail is not accepted everywhere",
        "body": "So I've been using proton as my mainemail provider for more than a year, almost 2\n\nbut sometimes I had to either drop some services/apps because they don't have sign up by email option or they have it but don't accept proton domain\n\nI tried disroot, but it wasn't enough either\n\nso I found back then that Yahoo although horrible for safety, but at least the least of evils as it's not on the official BDS\n\nand it's recognized enough,\n\nBUT, I learnt today that it's categorized as red in gaza . nu although not on the official bds\n\nTL;DR\n\nSo my question is there a provider that is recognized enough yet Israeli-safe",
        "keywords": {
            "protonmail": 1,
            "accepted": 1,
            "everywhere": 1,
            "using": 1,
            "proton": 2,
            "mainemail": 1,
            "provider": 2,
            "year": 1,
            "almost": 1,
            "2": 1,
            "sometimes": 1,
            "either": 2,
            "drop": 1,
            "sign": 1,
            "email": 1,
            "option": 1,
            "accept": 1,
            "domain": 1,
            "tried": 1,
            "disroot": 1,
            "enough": 3,
            "found": 1,
            "back": 1,
            "yahoo": 1,
            "although": 2,
            "horrible": 1,
            "safety": 1,
            "least": 2,
            "evil": 1,
            "official": 2,
            "bd": 2,
            "recognized": 2,
            "learnt": 1,
            "today": 1,
            "categorized": 1,
            "red": 1,
            "gaza": 1,
            "nu": 1,
            "tl": 1,
            "dr": 1,
            "question": 1,
            "yet": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Protonmail",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "more than a year",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "almost 2",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Yahoo",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "BDS",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "today",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "gaza",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israeli",
                "label": "NORP"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1spw1z8": {
        "id": "t3_1spw1z8",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-19T15:28:18.744Z",
        "title": "RISC-V (Opensource ISA) 2026 update",
        "body": "This video from Explaining Computers gives an update in 2026 on the development of the opensource RISC-V ISA (instruction set architecture).\n\nCurrently, most PCs and laptops use Intel, Nvidia, or AMD chips which run on x86 architecture. And most mobiles and Apple devices run on Qualcomm's chips, MediaTek's chips, or Apple's A-series / M-series chips all of which which run on ARM architecture.\n\nThe x86 and ARM architectures are both closed source and require licenses to develop chips based on them - from Intel and ARM Holdings (which is owned by SoftBank Group), respectively.\n\nIntel, Nvidia, and AMD are all boycott worthy and have deep ties with Israeli companies - Intel is a BDS Priority target. Out of these three, AMD is least worst.\n\nARM (SoftBank Group), Qualcomm, Apple are all also boycott worthy. MediaTek seems to be safe, but someone can correct me on that.\n\nThe RISC-V architecture is opensource and is currently used in niche and other less common devices.\n\nWhilst it may not be ready for them yet, in the coming years, we may see PCs, laptops, mobiles, and other modern electronic devices made with chips using RISC-V architecture.\n\nThe video mentions some manufacturers, companies, and organisations also involved in developing for RISC-V - some safe, some unsafe, some unknown.",
        "keywords": {
            "opensource": 3,
            "isa": 2,
            "2026": 2,
            "update": 2,
            "video": 2,
            "explaining": 1,
            "computer": 1,
            "give": 1,
            "development": 1,
            "instruction": 1,
            "set": 1,
            "architecture": 6,
            "currently": 2,
            "pc": 2,
            "laptop": 2,
            "use": 1,
            "intel": 4,
            "nvidia": 2,
            "amd": 3,
            "chip": 6,
            "run": 3,
            "x86": 2,
            "mobile": 2,
            "apple": 3,
            "device": 3,
            "qualcomm": 2,
            "mediatek": 2,
            "arm": 4,
            "closed": 1,
            "source": 1,
            "require": 1,
            "license": 1,
            "develop": 1,
            "based": 1,
            "holding": 1,
            "owned": 1,
            "softbank": 2,
            "group": 2,
            "respectively": 1,
            "boycott": 2,
            "worthy": 2,
            "deep": 1,
            "tie": 1,
            "israeli": 1,
            "company": 2,
            "bd": 1,
            "priority": 1,
            "target": 1,
            "three": 1,
            "least": 1,
            "worst": 1,
            "seems": 1,
            "safe": 2,
            "correct": 1,
            "used": 1,
            "niche": 1,
            "less": 1,
            "common": 1,
            "whilst": 1,
            "ready": 1,
            "yet": 1,
            "coming": 1,
            "year": 1,
            "see": 1,
            "modern": 1,
            "electronic": 1,
            "using": 1,
            "mention": 1,
            "manufacturer": 1,
            "organisation": 1,
            "involved": 1,
            "developing": 1,
            "unsafe": 1,
            "unknown": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "2026",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Explaining Computers",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "2026",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "ISA",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Intel",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Nvidia",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "AMD",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Apple",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Qualcomm",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "MediaTek",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Apple",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Intel",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "ARM Holdings",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "SoftBank Group",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Intel",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Nvidia",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "AMD",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israeli",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Intel",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "BDS Priority",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "three",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "AMD",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "SoftBank Group",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Qualcomm",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Apple",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "MediaTek",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "the coming years",
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1sqpm2r": {
        "id": "t3_1sqpm2r",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-20T13:38:40.552Z",
        "title": "Alternative list ? Help needed",
        "body": "Hello everyone, I've been searching for an entertainment app like netflix. according to the no thanks app (which truly is a blessing btw) almost everything is on the boycott list. Please help a buddy out 😛",
        "keywords": {
            "alternative": 1,
            "list": 2,
            "help": 2,
            "needed": 1,
            "hello": 1,
            "everyone": 1,
            "searching": 1,
            "entertainment": 1,
            "app": 2,
            "netflix": 1,
            "according": 1,
            "thanks": 1,
            "truly": 1,
            "blessing": 1,
            "btw": 1,
            "almost": 1,
            "everything": 1,
            "boycott": 1,
            "please": 1,
            "buddy": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Positive",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "netflix",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1so1m3h": {
        "id": "t3_1so1m3h",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-17T13:51:44.030Z",
        "title": "Does Joe & The Juice support israel?",
        "body": "I’ve seen a video on instagram of protestors going against Joe & The Juice in Lebanon because their support of israel, but I can’t find any info about the reason? It’s a Danish comp and not publicly traded, so does anyone have any more information?",
        "keywords": {
            "joe": 2,
            "juice": 2,
            "support": 2,
            "israel": 2,
            "seen": 1,
            "video": 1,
            "instagram": 1,
            "protestors": 1,
            "going": 1,
            "lebanon": 1,
            "find": 1,
            "info": 1,
            "reason": 1,
            "danish": 1,
            "comp": 1,
            "publicly": 1,
            "traded": 1,
            "information": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Joe & The Juice",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Lebanon",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Danish",
                "label": "NORP"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1spolb8": {
        "id": "t3_1spolb8",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-19T09:47:09.896Z",
        "title": "Remember to always carry your watermelons with you if you ever encounter them.",
        "body": "",
        "keywords": {
            "remember": 1,
            "always": 1,
            "carry": 1,
            "watermelon": 1,
            "ever": 1,
            "encounter": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Positive",
        "entities": []
    },
    "t3_1snr3sv": {
        "id": "t3_1snr3sv",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-17T04:53:16.586Z",
        "title": "Safe music streaming platforms?",
        "body": "Apple, spotify and amazon all are on the boycott list, are there any good music streaming platforms that are ethical?",
        "keywords": {
            "safe": 1,
            "music": 2,
            "streaming": 2,
            "platform": 2,
            "apple": 1,
            "spotify": 1,
            "amazon": 1,
            "boycott": 1,
            "list": 1,
            "good": 1,
            "ethical": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Apple",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1sovalw": {
        "id": "t3_1sovalw",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-18T11:37:44.198Z",
        "title": "loreal elvive alternatives?",
        "body": "hello! I’ve been boycotting for a while now but recently looking up hair product recommendations and all I’m getting is loreal elvive…does anybody have any alternatives for their hylaroun line please?",
        "keywords": {
            "loreal": 2,
            "elvive": 1,
            "alternative": 2,
            "hello": 1,
            "boycotting": 1,
            "recently": 1,
            "looking": 1,
            "hair": 1,
            "product": 1,
            "recommendation": 1,
            "anybody": 1,
            "hylaroun": 1,
            "line": 1,
            "please": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": []
    },
    "t3_1snhimv": {
        "id": "t3_1snhimv",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-16T21:46:14.437Z",
        "title": "Nail Polish Brands you recommend",
        "body": "I’ve been looking to get some new nail polish but the only two brands I was considering ship to you know where, I’m considering emailing them to inquire as to why but in the meantime if there are any brands you recommend I’d appreciate it. I’m looking for a glass nail file as well so a brand that also has one of those would be appreciated.",
        "keywords": {
            "nail": 3,
            "polish": 2,
            "brand": 4,
            "recommend": 2,
            "looking": 2,
            "new": 1,
            "two": 1,
            "considering": 2,
            "ship": 1,
            "emailing": 1,
            "inquire": 1,
            "meantime": 1,
            "appreciate": 1,
            "glass": 1,
            "file": 1,
            "well": 1,
            "one": 1,
            "appreciated": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Polish",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "only two",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1snpl93": {
        "id": "t3_1snpl93",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-17T03:38:04.280Z",
        "title": "I feel guilty bc the dates I ordered ended up being Israeli, what should I do",
        "body": "So my family gets our regular groceries delivered, which means I can’t rlly check where the product is from, I usually get dates from a local market cuz they’re a bit cheaper, and the owners of the stall are, I believe, Lebanese. Which I imagine would mean non-Israeli dates but now that I think of it I should double check and look at the boxes they’re in. Anyway, the market isn’t available for a bit so I just tacked them on the order cuz last time I saw them in the store they were all Moroccan. Delivery came and I was out so when I got home everything was already unpacked by family, including the dates. I had it nagging in my head to make sure so I found the packaging in the bin and saw they were a “product of israel”.\n\nI haven’t eaten them yet but I just feel really guilty now havent inadvertently helped israeli profits and shi the store a demand for a product they sometimes source from israel, but I don’t wanna encourage that.\n\nI know it probably is minor compared to everything else but I just wanted some opinions on what other people would do, since they’ve bee opened and moved it’s not like I can return and refund them to then not be giving my money to them, so idk if anything will make me not get feel guilty about it now, I’ve debated binning the but also feel like that would be dumb to just waste food especially when others across the world and in Palestine are being starved, it would feel hypocritical yk? But I’d feel like a twat for snacking on an israeli product. What should I do?\n\nAny suggestions on how to make sure my dates in future are not israeli, even at local grocery markets, specifically for the UK if possible?",
        "keywords": {
            "feel": 6,
            "guilty": 3,
            "bc": 1,
            "date": 5,
            "ordered": 1,
            "ended": 1,
            "israeli": 4,
            "family": 2,
            "get": 1,
            "regular": 1,
            "grocery": 2,
            "delivered": 1,
            "mean": 2,
            "rlly": 1,
            "check": 2,
            "product": 4,
            "usually": 1,
            "local": 2,
            "market": 3,
            "cuz": 2,
            "bit": 2,
            "cheaper": 1,
            "owner": 1,
            "stall": 1,
            "believe": 1,
            "lebanese": 1,
            "imagine": 1,
            "think": 1,
            "double": 1,
            "box": 1,
            "anyway": 1,
            "available": 1,
            "tacked": 1,
            "order": 1,
            "last": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "saw": 2,
            "store": 2,
            "moroccan": 1,
            "delivery": 1,
            "came": 1,
            "home": 1,
            "everything": 2,
            "already": 1,
            "unpacked": 1,
            "including": 1,
            "nagging": 1,
            "head": 1,
            "sure": 2,
            "found": 1,
            "packaging": 1,
            "bin": 1,
            "israel": 2,
            "eaten": 1,
            "yet": 1,
            "havent": 1,
            "inadvertently": 1,
            "helped": 1,
            "profit": 1,
            "shi": 1,
            "demand": 1,
            "sometimes": 1,
            "source": 1,
            "wan": 1,
            "na": 1,
            "encourage": 1,
            "minor": 1,
            "compared": 1,
            "else": 1,
            "opinion": 1,
            "people": 1,
            "since": 1,
            "bee": 1,
            "opened": 1,
            "moved": 1,
            "return": 1,
            "refund": 1,
            "giving": 1,
            "money": 1,
            "idk": 1,
            "anything": 1,
            "debated": 1,
            "binning": 1,
            "dumb": 1,
            "waste": 1,
            "food": 1,
            "especially": 1,
            "others": 1,
            "across": 1,
            "world": 1,
            "palestine": 1,
            "starved": 1,
            "hypocritical": 1,
            "yk": 1,
            "twat": 1,
            "snacking": 1,
            "suggestion": 1,
            "future": 1,
            "specifically": 1,
            "uk": 1,
            "possible": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Israeli",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Lebanese",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "non-Israeli",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Moroccan",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "bin",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "israeli",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Palestine",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "israeli",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "israeli",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "UK",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1sn829c": {
        "id": "t3_1sn829c",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-16T16:10:21.432Z",
        "title": "Record breaking signing petition",
        "body": "Sharing in case someone here can put their hand in. This is the link: Click here or type 'EU petition israel'",
        "keywords": {
            "record": 1,
            "breaking": 1,
            "signing": 1,
            "petition": 2,
            "sharing": 1,
            "case": 1,
            "put": 1,
            "hand": 1,
            "link": 1,
            "click": 1,
            "type": 1,
            "israel": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Sharing",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "EU",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1snb6js": {
        "id": "t3_1snb6js",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-16T17:58:29.071Z",
        "title": "Why was the post including Isn'treal supporting celebs deleted? Is there another like it?",
        "body": "There was a post on this subreddit with a list of celebrities who support Palestine nd the ones who support Isn'treal. It seems to have been removed. Can anyone provide another such list? Thanks in advance.",
        "keywords": {
            "including": 1,
            "supporting": 1,
            "celebs": 1,
            "another": 2,
            "list": 2,
            "celebrity": 1,
            "support": 2,
            "palestine": 1,
            "nd": 1,
            "one": 1,
            "seems": 1,
            "provide": 1,
            "thanks": 1,
            "advance": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Palestine",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1slsbpu": {
        "id": "t3_1slsbpu",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-15T01:47:15.250Z",
        "title": "Uk skincare?",
        "body": "Hello! I’ve been boycotting the bigger companies and shops for quite a while now, however I have just learned that boots has ties to Isreal. I have been trying to find out if Superdrug also supports Isreal, as they are my only two options near me. If anyone has any information that I am unaware of, please do let me know!",
        "keywords": {
            "uk": 1,
            "skincare": 1,
            "hello": 1,
            "boycotting": 1,
            "bigger": 1,
            "company": 1,
            "shop": 1,
            "however": 1,
            "learned": 1,
            "boot": 1,
            "tie": 1,
            "isreal": 2,
            "trying": 1,
            "find": 1,
            "superdrug": 1,
            "support": 1,
            "two": 1,
            "option": 1,
            "near": 1,
            "information": 1,
            "unaware": 1,
            "please": 1,
            "let": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Uk",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Superdrug",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Isreal",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "only two",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1slofgp": {
        "id": "t3_1slofgp",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-14T22:57:18.265Z",
        "title": "They showed up first… but nobody talks about what happened next",
        "body": "",
        "keywords": {
            "showed": 1,
            "nobody": 1,
            "talk": 1,
            "happened": 1,
            "next": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "first",
                "label": "ORDINAL"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1sm8bl7": {
        "id": "t3_1sm8bl7",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-15T14:51:26.685Z",
        "title": "Say NO to the Orange Genocide: Boycott easyJet at Eurovision Song Contest 2026",
        "body": "Why you should boycott:\n\nThe campaign by Catrin Feelings will focus on 35 countries and its slogan ''Get Out There'' for the participating countries, including on support Israel's participation for the event.\n\nThe airline's funding was contributed with Martin Green in support of the EBU to give its extension deal since 2024. It is already known that the main beauty partner MoroccanOil is currently already on target.\n\nFive countries Spain, Ireland, the Netherlands, Slovenia and Iceland have withdrawn from the competition in protest of Israel's participation. The campaign to have exclusion on those countries as easyJet travels to those countries only outside Eurovision to do so.\n\nLinks to target:\n\nhttps://www.facebook.com/share/r/1Now8aEEZY/\n\nhttps://www.instagram.com/easyjet/reel/DXJukrqD0TS/\n\nhttps://www.youtube.com/shorts/WdghLLqQues\n\nhttps://www.tiktok.com/@easyjet/video/7628958948766321953\n\nGoals:\n\nBlock Catrin Feelings on Instagram, Spotify and all other accounts on social media if you are planning not to watch Eurovision 2026.\n\nContact with rte.ie, rtve.es, rtvslo.si, ruv.is and avrotros.nl at GMail on to file of complaint for easyJet's Eurovision 2026 campaign has a connection with Israel's participation for the event.\n\nKey comments to write on Instagram, Youtube, Facebook and TikTok after you found the link: #noeasyjetforeurovision, #boycotteasyjet #pinkwashing, #moneytalks, 🇪🇸🇮🇪🇳🇱🇸🇮🇮🇸, and multiple times of 🇵🇸🇵🇸🇵🇸🇵🇸🇵🇸🇵🇸.\n\nKeep in mind on support gaza.nu, disoccupied.com and nothanks.app\n\nNoting that I have delayed the boycott campaign earlier by being today, instead of April 16th CEST 00:00 due to my important sleep at midnight and my other personal reasons.",
        "keywords": {
            "say": 1,
            "orange": 1,
            "genocide": 1,
            "boycott": 3,
            "easyjet": 3,
            "eurovision": 4,
            "song": 1,
            "contest": 1,
            "2026": 2,
            "campaign": 4,
            "catrin": 2,
            "feeling": 2,
            "focus": 1,
            "35": 1,
            "country": 5,
            "slogan": 1,
            "participating": 1,
            "including": 1,
            "support": 3,
            "israel": 3,
            "participation": 3,
            "event": 2,
            "airline": 1,
            "funding": 1,
            "contributed": 1,
            "martin": 1,
            "green": 1,
            "ebu": 1,
            "give": 1,
            "extension": 1,
            "deal": 1,
            "since": 1,
            "already": 2,
            "known": 1,
            "main": 1,
            "beauty": 1,
            "partner": 1,
            "moroccanoil": 1,
            "currently": 1,
            "target": 2,
            "five": 1,
            "spain": 1,
            "ireland": 1,
            "netherlands": 1,
            "slovenia": 1,
            "iceland": 1,
            "withdrawn": 1,
            "competition": 1,
            "protest": 1,
            "exclusion": 1,
            "travel": 1,
            "outside": 1,
            "link": 2,
            "goal": 1,
            "block": 1,
            "instagram": 2,
            "spotify": 1,
            "account": 1,
            "social": 1,
            "medium": 1,
            "planning": 1,
            "watch": 1,
            "contact": 1,
            "gmail": 1,
            "file": 1,
            "complaint": 1,
            "connection": 1,
            "key": 1,
            "write": 1,
            "youtube": 1,
            "facebook": 1,
            "tiktok": 1,
            "found": 1,
            "noeasyjetforeurovision": 1,
            "boycotteasyjet": 1,
            "pinkwashing": 1,
            "moneytalks": 1,
            "multiple": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "keep": 1,
            "mind": 1,
            "noting": 1,
            "delayed": 1,
            "earlier": 1,
            "today": 1,
            "instead": 1,
            "april": 1,
            "16th": 1,
            "cest": 1,
            "due": 1,
            "important": 1,
            "sleep": 1,
            "midnight": 1,
            "personal": 1,
            "reason": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "the Orange Genocide: Boycott easyJet",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "2026",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Catrin Feelings",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "35",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Get Out There''",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Martin Green",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "EBU",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "2024",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "MoroccanOil",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Five",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Spain",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Ireland",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Netherlands",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Slovenia",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Iceland",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Instagram",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Spotify",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Eurovision 2026",
                "label": "LAW"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Instagram",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Youtube",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "TikTok",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "#",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "🇪",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "🇮",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "🇸",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "🇮🇮🇸",
                "label": "PRODUCT"
            },
            {
                "text": "🇵🇸",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "🇸🇵",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "🇸🇵",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "🇸🇵",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "🇸🇵",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "🇸",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "today",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "April 16th",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "midnight",
                "label": "TIME"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1slhbrm": {
        "id": "t3_1slhbrm",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-14T18:34:36.883Z",
        "title": "Should caprisun be boycotted?",
        "body": "I have a question about capri-sun\n\nI have doubts about if caprisun is boycott or no because the american caprisun is owned by kraft and the european is owned by capri sun group holding ag so i wanted to ask",
        "keywords": {
            "caprisun": 3,
            "boycotted": 1,
            "question": 1,
            "doubt": 1,
            "boycott": 1,
            "american": 1,
            "owned": 2,
            "kraft": 1,
            "european": 1,
            "capri": 1,
            "sun": 1,
            "group": 1,
            "holding": 1,
            "ag": 1,
            "ask": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "american",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "european",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "capri sun",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "ag",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1sl7jjl": {
        "id": "t3_1sl7jjl",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-14T12:40:33.479Z",
        "title": "Vitacost magnesium oxide",
        "body": "I just noticed that the Vitacost Everyday brand magnesium oxide is a product of Israel. It’s a small thing but I will not be buying this again. I also left a review on their site mentioning it.",
        "keywords": {
            "vitacost": 2,
            "magnesium": 2,
            "oxide": 2,
            "noticed": 1,
            "everyday": 1,
            "brand": 1,
            "product": 1,
            "israel": 1,
            "small": 1,
            "buying": 1,
            "left": 1,
            "review": 1,
            "site": 1,
            "mentioning": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Vitacost Everyday",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Israel",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1skyfnd": {
        "id": "t3_1skyfnd",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-14T04:30:53.447Z",
        "title": "Ms Rachel toys I saw at Kohl",
        "body": "",
        "keywords": {
            "m": 1,
            "rachel": 1,
            "toy": 1,
            "saw": 1,
            "kohl": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Ms Rachel",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Kohl",
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1skwr7c": {
        "id": "t3_1skwr7c",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-14T03:09:34.659Z",
        "title": "For those looking for alternatives: use bowl and basket!",
        "body": "I buy from this company called Bowl and Basket, and they sell over 3,500 alternatives! The down side is, they're a private label brand and are only sold at these stores:\n\nPrice Rite Marketplace\n\nThe Fresh Grocer\n\nFairway Market\n\nGourmet Garage\n\nDearborn Market ",
        "keywords": {
            "looking": 1,
            "alternative": 2,
            "use": 1,
            "bowl": 2,
            "basket": 2,
            "buy": 1,
            "company": 1,
            "called": 1,
            "sell": 1,
            "side": 1,
            "private": 1,
            "label": 1,
            "brand": 1,
            "sold": 1,
            "store": 1,
            "price": 1,
            "rite": 1,
            "marketplace": 1,
            "fresh": 1,
            "grocer": 1,
            "fairway": 1,
            "market": 2,
            "gourmet": 1,
            "garage": 1,
            "dearborn": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Bowl",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
            },
            {
                "text": "3,500",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Rite Marketplace",
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1skqkl7": {
        "id": "t3_1skqkl7",
        "timestamp": "2026-04-13T22:42:02.506Z",
        "title": "Allergy season help? What OTC meds and medical supplies would would be good alternatives to pro-genocide meds/supplies companies and brands?",
