{
    "t3_1t5k4b2": {
        "id": "t3_1t5k4b2",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-06T17:42:39.044Z",
        "title": "Volunteer work for english speakers searched!",
        "body": "Hello!\n\nI'm interested in doing volunteer work in Munich, anything related to helping others or the environment would be great! I only speak english and spanish so if someone could help me find something that doesn't require me to speak german I would greatly appreciate it\n\nThanks!",
        "keywords": {
            "volunteer": 2,
            "work": 2,
            "english": 2,
            "speaker": 1,
            "searched": 1,
            "hello": 1,
            "interested": 1,
            "munich": 1,
            "anything": 1,
            "related": 1,
            "helping": 1,
            "others": 1,
            "environment": 1,
            "great": 1,
            "speak": 2,
            "spanish": 1,
            "help": 1,
            "find": 1,
            "something": 1,
            "require": 1,
            "german": 1,
            "greatly": 1,
            "appreciate": 1,
            "thanks": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Positive",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Volunteer",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "english",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "english",
                "label": "LANGUAGE"
            },
            {
                "text": "spanish",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "german",
                "label": "NORP"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t5k6ge": {
        "id": "t3_1t5k6ge",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-06T17:44:39.672Z",
        "title": "Meetingraum und schönes Restaurant gesucht",
        "body": "Hallo,\n\nich organisiere ein Meeting in München (ca. 15-20 Personen), welches abends stattfinden soll. Im Anschluss wäre ein gemeinsames Abendessen geplant.\n\nKann jemand einen Meetingraum oder Hotel mit Meetingräumen empfehlen, in welchem sich im Anschluss auch gut essen lässt? Die Location sollte idealerweise im Raum Sendlinger Tor/Goetheplatz/Theresienwiese liegen und gut angebunden sein. Gute Parkmöglichkeiten wären ein Plus.\n\nLieben Dank für Eure Tipps 😊",
        "keywords": {
            "meetingraum": 2,
            "und": 2,
            "schönes": 1,
            "restaurant": 1,
            "gesucht": 1,
            "hallo": 1,
            "ich": 1,
            "organisiere": 1,
            "ein": 3,
            "meeting": 1,
            "münchen": 1,
            "ca": 1,
            "personen": 1,
            "welches": 1,
            "abends": 1,
            "stattfinden": 1,
            "soll": 1,
            "im": 3,
            "anschluss": 2,
            "wäre": 1,
            "gemeinsames": 1,
            "abendessen": 1,
            "geplant": 1,
            "kann": 1,
            "jemand": 1,
            "einen": 1,
            "oder": 1,
            "hotel": 1,
            "mit": 1,
            "meetingräumen": 1,
            "empfehlen": 1,
            "welchem": 1,
            "sich": 1,
            "auch": 1,
            "gut": 2,
            "essen": 1,
            "lässt": 1,
            "die": 1,
            "location": 1,
            "sollte": 1,
            "idealerweise": 1,
            "raum": 1,
            "sendlinger": 1,
            "liegen": 1,
            "angebunden": 1,
            "sein": 1,
            "gute": 1,
            "parkmöglichkeiten": 1,
            "wären": 1,
            "plus": 1,
            "lieben": 1,
            "dank": 1,
            "für": 1,
            "eure": 1,
            "tipps": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Meetingraum",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "München",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "15-20",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Personen",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Anschluss",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Abendessen",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Kann",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Meetingraum",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Hotel mit Meetingräumen",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Anschluss",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Raum Sendlinger",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Tor/Goetheplatz/Theresienwiese",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Lieben Dank",
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t5psm2": {
        "id": "t3_1t5psm2",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-06T21:02:32.279Z",
        "title": "Glutenfree Snacks?",
        "body": "Hi!\n\nI'm invited to a friend's birthday party soon.\n\nI already have her main gift, but want to gift her some gluten free snacks as well - maybe some good cookies?\n\nAny recommendations where I can get a good variety of glutenfree snacks in Munich?\n\nDoes Dallmayr carry any?",
        "keywords": {
            "glutenfree": 2,
            "snack": 3,
            "hi": 1,
            "invited": 1,
            "friend": 1,
            "birthday": 1,
            "party": 1,
            "soon": 1,
            "already": 1,
            "main": 1,
            "gift": 2,
            "gluten": 1,
            "free": 1,
            "well": 1,
            "good": 2,
            "cooky": 1,
            "recommendation": 1,
            "variety": 1,
            "munich": 1,
            "dallmayr": 1,
            "carry": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Positive",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Dallmayr",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ],
        "last_cached": true
    },
    "t3_1t5euav": {
        "id": "t3_1t5euav",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-06T14:38:27.186Z",
        "title": "Need some travel advice",
        "body": "Is this doable?\nI am a 17 year old tourist visiting Munich with my family (Dad 46M, Mom 44F and sister 10F) on the 17th and 18th of May and plan on doing the following things. Is it feasible? I know it fast-paced but I like travelling that way.\n\nMay 17th\nTrain from Düsseldorf at 5:30 arriving in Munich at 10:30. Make a quick visit (3 hours max) to the BMW museum. Take the RE5 to Salzburg at around 4 PM, spend the evening there and return to Munich via the last RE5 from Salzburg to Munich\n\nMay 18th\nVisit Schwangau, take the cable car up to the Tegelberg and hike down to Füssen via the Marienbrücke. Return to Munich, explore the old town for a bit (Maybe visit the Nymphenburg Palace if time permits) and catch an ICE back to Düsseldorf at around midnight.\n\nPlease give me your valuable suggestions and thanks in advance.",
        "keywords": {
            "need": 1,
            "travel": 1,
            "advice": 1,
            "doable": 1,
            "17": 1,
            "year": 1,
            "old": 2,
            "tourist": 1,
            "visiting": 1,
            "munich": 5,
            "family": 1,
            "dad": 1,
            "46m": 1,
            "mom": 1,
            "44f": 1,
            "sister": 1,
            "10f": 1,
            "17th": 2,
            "18th": 2,
            "plan": 1,
            "following": 1,
            "feasible": 1,
            "travelling": 1,
            "way": 1,
            "train": 1,
            "düsseldorf": 2,
            "arriving": 1,
            "quick": 1,
            "visit": 3,
            "3": 1,
            "hour": 1,
            "max": 1,
            "bmw": 1,
            "museum": 1,
            "re5": 2,
            "salzburg": 2,
            "around": 2,
            "4": 1,
            "pm": 1,
            "spend": 1,
            "evening": 1,
            "return": 2,
            "via": 2,
            "last": 1,
            "schwangau": 1,
            "cable": 1,
            "car": 1,
            "tegelberg": 1,
            "hike": 1,
            "füssen": 1,
            "marienbrücke": 1,
            "explore": 1,
            "town": 1,
            "bit": 1,
            "nymphenburg": 1,
            "palace": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "permit": 1,
            "catch": 1,
            "ice": 1,
            "back": 1,
            "midnight": 1,
            "please": 1,
            "give": 1,
            "valuable": 1,
            "suggestion": 1,
            "thanks": 1,
            "advance": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "17 year old",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "10F",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "the 17th and 18th of May",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "May 17th",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "5:30",
                "label": "TIME"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "10:30",
                "label": "TIME"
            },
            {
                "text": "3 hours",
                "label": "TIME"
            },
            {
                "text": "max",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "BMW",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Salzburg",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "4 PM",
                "label": "TIME"
            },
            {
                "text": "the evening",
                "label": "TIME"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Salzburg",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "May 18th",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Tegelberg",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Füssen",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "the Nymphenburg Palace",
                "label": "FAC"
            },
            {
                "text": "Düsseldorf",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "around midnight",
                "label": "TIME"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t5e7m8": {
        "id": "t3_1t5e7m8",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-06T14:15:19.191Z",
        "title": "Wo in der Münchner Innenstadt kann ich diese CO2 Flasche zurückgeben? Müsste eine Kaufflasche ohne Pfand sein und eine neue brauche ich auch nicht.",
        "body": "",
        "keywords": {
            "wo": 1,
            "der": 1,
            "münchner": 1,
            "innenstadt": 1,
            "kann": 1,
            "ich": 2,
            "diese": 1,
            "co2": 1,
            "flasche": 1,
            "zurückgeben": 1,
            "müsste": 1,
            "eine": 2,
            "kaufflasche": 1,
            "ohne": 1,
            "pfand": 1,
            "sein": 1,
            "und": 1,
            "neue": 1,
            "brauche": 1,
            "auch": 1,
            "nicht": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Münchner Innenstadt",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "diese",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "CO2 Flasche",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Kaufflasche",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Pfand",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "neue brauche",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t5g8tg": {
        "id": "t3_1t5g8tg",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-06T15:29:02.883Z",
        "title": "Does Bavarian ticket from Munich to Salzburg at end of May guarantees a place on the train?",
        "body": "Hello. I am currently in planning stages for my trip to Munich at end of May, during which I am planning to spend one day going to Salzburg in early morning and back in evening.\n\nFrom what I read, the best option (please correct me if I am wrong) appears to be to get the Bavarian ticket. It comes in at 34 euros for the day and if I am reading the policy right, it essentially means I can board either RE and RB train types at any time with no fixed schedule.\n\nBut also if I read it correctly, this means no seat reservation. Does this imply that I only can board the train if there is space and priority would be given to people having bought a fixed ticket with a seat reservation? Or this doesn't matter?\n\nIn other words, does the Bavarian ticket come with a risk that I might not get a spot on the train?\n\nedit : Thanks everyone for the replies!",
        "keywords": {
            "bavarian": 3,
            "ticket": 4,
            "munich": 2,
            "salzburg": 2,
            "end": 2,
            "guarantee": 1,
            "place": 1,
            "train": 4,
            "hello": 1,
            "currently": 1,
            "planning": 2,
            "stage": 1,
            "trip": 1,
            "spend": 1,
            "one": 1,
            "day": 2,
            "going": 1,
            "early": 1,
            "morning": 1,
            "back": 1,
            "evening": 1,
            "read": 2,
            "best": 1,
            "option": 1,
            "please": 1,
            "correct": 1,
            "wrong": 1,
            "appears": 1,
            "come": 2,
            "34": 1,
            "euro": 1,
            "reading": 1,
            "policy": 1,
            "right": 1,
            "essentially": 1,
            "mean": 2,
            "board": 2,
            "either": 1,
            "rb": 1,
            "type": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "fixed": 2,
            "schedule": 1,
            "correctly": 1,
            "seat": 2,
            "reservation": 2,
            "imply": 1,
            "space": 1,
            "priority": 1,
            "given": 1,
            "people": 1,
            "bought": 1,
            "matter": 1,
            "word": 1,
            "risk": 1,
            "spot": 1,
            "thanks": 1,
            "everyone": 1,
            "reply": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Bavarian",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Salzburg",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "May",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "May",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "one day",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Salzburg",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "early morning",
                "label": "TIME"
            },
            {
                "text": "evening",
                "label": "TIME"
            },
            {
                "text": "Bavarian",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "34",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "the day",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Bavarian",
                "label": "NORP"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t5ay3c": {
        "id": "t3_1t5ay3c",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-06T12:07:14.565Z",
        "title": "Right now I'm am on a U-Bahn that looks like from the 60s-70s, is that a regular occurrence in U-Bahn Service?",
        "body": "I wish I could take a photo but it's crowded so I can't but I tried to take a pic of the window panel (hopefully no one was bothered). I thought these are long retired from service and have been dismantled and disposed of. This is a completely new experience for me!",
        "keywords": {
            "right": 1,
            "regular": 1,
            "occurrence": 1,
            "service": 2,
            "wish": 1,
            "photo": 1,
            "crowded": 1,
            "ca": 1,
            "tried": 1,
            "pic": 1,
            "window": 1,
            "panel": 1,
            "hopefully": 1,
            "one": 1,
            "bothered": 1,
            "thought": 1,
            "long": 1,
            "retired": 1,
            "dismantled": 1,
            "disposed": 1,
            "completely": 1,
            "new": 1,
            "experience": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "U-Bahn",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "the 60s-70s",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "U-Bahn Service",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t5dpwt": {
        "id": "t3_1t5dpwt",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-06T13:57:28.894Z",
        "title": "Searching for Fashion Designs for examination – Dancers miming flowers (Munich June, 23th to 29th)",
        "body": "🇬🇧\n\nHello all,\n\nin June 2026, I will be sitting an exam in photography (non-commercial project). For this, I am looking for fashion designs that will support me in my photography project.\n\nI would like to photograph dancers who, through their posture and the garments they wear, mimic the shapes of blossoms.\n\nIf you have a suitable design and live near Munich, I would be delighted to have your support!\n\nFor me, help and support isn’t a one-way street! As a thank you, I’d love to support you with a photoshoot for your next project!\n\nIf you’re interested, please do get in touch for more details via personal message!!\n\nThank you so much!!\n\n🇩🇪\n\nHallo zusammen,\n\nim Juni 2026 werde ich eine Prüfung im Fach Fotografie (nicht-kommerzielles Projekt) ablegen. Dafür suche ich Modedesigns, die mich bei meinem Fotoprojekt unterstützen.\n\nIch möchte Tänzerinnen und Tänzer fotografieren, die durch ihre Körperhaltung und die Kleidung, die sie tragen, die Formen von Blüten nachahmen.\n\nWenn ihr ein passendes Design habt und in der Nähe von München wohnt, würde ich mich sehr über eure Unterstützung freuen!\n\nFür mich ist Hilfe und Unterstützung keine Einbahnstraße! Als Dankeschön würde ich dich gerne mit einem Fotoshooting für dein nächstes Projekt unterstützen!\n\nWenn du Interesse hast, melde dich bitte per Direktnachricht, um weitere Details zu erfahren!!\n\nVielen Dank!!",
        "keywords": {
            "searching": 1,
            "fashion": 2,
            "design": 4,
            "examination": 1,
            "dancer": 2,
            "miming": 1,
            "flower": 1,
            "munich": 2,
            "june": 2,
            "23th": 1,
            "29th": 1,
            "hello": 1,
            "2026": 2,
            "sitting": 1,
            "exam": 1,
            "photography": 2,
            "project": 3,
            "looking": 1,
            "support": 4,
            "photograph": 1,
            "posture": 1,
            "garment": 1,
            "wear": 1,
            "mimic": 1,
            "shape": 1,
            "blossom": 1,
            "suitable": 1,
            "live": 1,
            "near": 1,
            "delighted": 1,
            "help": 1,
            "street": 1,
            "thank": 2,
            "love": 1,
            "photoshoot": 1,
            "next": 1,
            "interested": 1,
            "please": 1,
            "touch": 1,
            "detail": 2,
            "via": 1,
            "personal": 1,
            "message": 1,
            "hallo": 1,
            "zusammen": 1,
            "im": 2,
            "juni": 1,
            "werde": 1,
            "ich": 5,
            "eine": 1,
            "prüfung": 1,
            "fach": 1,
            "fotografie": 1,
            "projekt": 2,
            "ablegen": 1,
            "dafür": 1,
            "suche": 1,
            "modedesigns": 1,
            "die": 5,
            "mich": 3,
            "bei": 1,
            "meinem": 1,
            "fotoprojekt": 1,
            "unterstützen": 2,
            "möchte": 1,
            "tänzerinnen": 1,
            "und": 4,
            "tänzer": 1,
            "fotografieren": 1,
            "durch": 1,
            "ihre": 1,
            "körperhaltung": 1,
            "kleidung": 1,
            "sie": 1,
            "tragen": 1,
            "formen": 1,
            "von": 2,
            "blüten": 1,
            "nachahmen": 1,
            "wenn": 2,
            "ihr": 1,
            "ein": 1,
            "passendes": 1,
            "habt": 1,
            "der": 1,
            "nähe": 1,
            "münchen": 1,
            "wohnt": 1,
            "würde": 2,
            "sehr": 1,
            "über": 1,
            "eure": 1,
            "unterstützung": 2,
            "freuen": 1,
            "für": 2,
            "ist": 1,
            "hilfe": 1,
            "keine": 1,
            "einbahnstraße": 1,
            "al": 1,
            "dankeschön": 1,
            "dich": 2,
            "gerne": 1,
            "mit": 1,
            "einem": 1,
            "fotoshooting": 1,
            "dein": 1,
            "nächstes": 1,
            "du": 1,
            "interesse": 1,
            "hast": 1,
            "melde": 1,
            "bitte": 1,
            "per": 1,
            "direktnachricht": 1,
            "um": 1,
            "weitere": 1,
            "zu": 1,
            "erfahren": 1,
            "vielen": 1,
            "dank": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "June",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "23th to 29th",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "June 2026",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "one",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "🇩🇪",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Hallo",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "2026",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "werde",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Prüfung",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Fach Fotografie",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Projekt",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Dafür",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Modedesigns",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "mich bei meinem",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Fotoprojekt",
                "label": "PRODUCT"
            },
            {
                "text": "Tänzerinnen",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Tänzer",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Körperhaltung",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Kleidung",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Formen von Blüten",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Wenn",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Design",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Nähe von München",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "würde",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "mich sehr über",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Unterstützung",
                "label": "PRODUCT"
            },
            {
                "text": "Hilfe",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Als Dankeschön",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Projekt",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Direktnachricht",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t56s9e": {
        "id": "t3_1t56s9e",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-06T08:26:27.889Z",
        "title": "Looking for dentist in Munich (GOZ ≤ 3.5, Zusatzversicherung friendly)",
        "body": "Hey, I’m looking for a dentist in Munich who usually charges within the GOZ limit (max 3.5x) for standard treatments like sealants or composite fillings etc..\n\nI have a private dental add-on insurance that reimburses 100% only up to 3.5x — anything above that I have to pay out of pocket, which kind of defeats the purpose of having it. My current dentist usually charges 4.2x so it doesn’t make sense for me to stay with him\n\nWould really appreciate any recommendations 🙏",
        "keywords": {
            "looking": 2,
            "dentist": 3,
            "munich": 2,
            "goz": 2,
            "zusatzversicherung": 1,
            "friendly": 1,
            "hey": 1,
            "usually": 2,
            "charge": 2,
            "within": 1,
            "limit": 1,
            "max": 1,
            "standard": 1,
            "treatment": 1,
            "sealant": 1,
            "composite": 1,
            "filling": 1,
            "etc": 1,
            "private": 1,
            "dental": 1,
            "insurance": 1,
            "reimburses": 1,
            "100": 1,
            "anything": 1,
            "pay": 1,
            "pocket": 1,
            "kind": 1,
            "defeat": 1,
            "purpose": 1,
            "current": 1,
            "sense": 1,
            "stay": 1,
            "appreciate": 1,
            "recommendation": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "GOZ ≤",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "3.5",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Zusatzversicherung",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "GOZ",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "max",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "100%",
                "label": "PERCENT"
            },
            {
                "text": "🙏",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t551rr": {
        "id": "t3_1t551rr",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-06T06:43:00.865Z",
        "title": "Help with retrieving lost headphones from Istanbul",
        "body": "If there's anyone travelling to Istanbul right now or very soon, I'd really appreciate your help! Unfortunately, I lost my headphones at a hotel and they found them, but shipping them to Munich turns out to be a bit of a hassle. If you might be able to help me, please reach out to me via DM!",
        "keywords": {
            "help": 3,
            "retrieving": 1,
            "lost": 2,
            "headphone": 2,
            "istanbul": 2,
            "travelling": 1,
            "right": 1,
            "soon": 1,
            "appreciate": 1,
            "unfortunately": 1,
            "hotel": 1,
            "found": 1,
            "shipping": 1,
            "munich": 1,
            "turn": 1,
            "bit": 1,
            "hassle": 1,
            "able": 1,
            "please": 1,
            "reach": 1,
            "via": 1,
            "dm": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Istanbul",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Istanbul",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "DM",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t58fyf": {
        "id": "t3_1t58fyf",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-06T10:04:44.914Z",
        "title": "Cycling store that rents out",
        "body": "Hey Guys I‘m looking for a cycling store in munich that rents out road bikes. Planning a trip next week and need a bike. Thanks!",
        "keywords": {
            "cycling": 2,
            "store": 2,
            "rent": 2,
            "hey": 1,
            "guy": 1,
            "looking": 1,
            "munich": 1,
            "road": 1,
            "bike": 2,
            "planning": 1,
            "trip": 1,
            "next": 1,
            "week": 1,
            "need": 1,
            "thanks": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Hey Guys",
                "label": "FAC"
            },
            {
                "text": "munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "next week",
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t4rxqe": {
        "id": "t3_1t4rxqe",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T20:46:54.093Z",
        "title": "Looking for Haribo Watermelon gummies in Munich",
        "body": "&#x200B;\n\n​Hi! I’m from Mexico, and last year my family traveled to Europe. Somewhere along the way—they can't remember if it was in Paris or Madrid—they bought me a large bag of Haribo Watermelon gummies, which I absolutely loved.\n\n​This year they are back in Europe visiting some new cities, including Munich. Unfortunately, they haven't been able to find that specific watermelon bag in Madrid or Paris; they've only seen other varieties of the brand.\n\n​I’m asking for your help! Since they are currently in Munich, where can they find large bags of these delicious watermelon gummies? Also, which other Haribo varieties do you consider to be the best?\n\n​Greetings from Cordoba, Veracruz, Mexico!",
        "keywords": {
            "looking": 1,
            "haribo": 3,
            "watermelon": 4,
            "gummies": 3,
            "munich": 3,
            "x200b": 1,
            "mexico": 2,
            "last": 1,
            "year": 2,
            "family": 1,
            "traveled": 1,
            "europe": 2,
            "somewhere": 1,
            "along": 1,
            "way": 1,
            "ca": 1,
            "remember": 1,
            "paris": 2,
            "madrid": 2,
            "bought": 1,
            "large": 2,
            "bag": 3,
            "absolutely": 1,
            "loved": 1,
            "back": 1,
            "visiting": 1,
            "new": 1,
            "city": 1,
            "including": 1,
            "unfortunately": 1,
            "able": 1,
            "find": 2,
            "specific": 1,
            "seen": 1,
            "variety": 2,
            "brand": 1,
            "asking": 1,
            "help": 1,
            "since": 1,
            "currently": 1,
            "delicious": 1,
            "consider": 1,
            "best": 1,
            "cordoba": 1,
            "veracruz": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Haribo Watermelon",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich &",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Mexico",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "last year",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Europe",
                "label": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "text": "Paris",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Madrid",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Haribo Watermelon",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Europe",
                "label": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Madrid",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Paris",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Haribo",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Cordoba",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Veracruz",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Mexico",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t54jhv": {
        "id": "t3_1t54jhv",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-06T06:13:53.306Z",
        "title": "Just hiked Herzogstand. A friend recommended Wank, which seems doable, and also Kramer. What would you recommend out of the two?",
        "body": "I went up Herzogstand yesterday in about 2 hours and hiked back down in about an hour or so. Relatively fit, but I’d consider myself a beginner. There were some rocky paths to get across but wasn’t too stressing.\n\nI’d like to go on another hike before I leave Munich. A local friend had recommended Wank, and from what I’ve seen, it looks leisurely for the most part. They recommended Kramer as the nicest option though. It seems intriguing but a lot more intimidating.\n\nWould Kramer be a bad idea for someone at my level and should I stick with Wank?",
        "keywords": {
            "hiked": 2,
            "herzogstand": 2,
            "friend": 2,
            "recommended": 3,
            "wank": 3,
            "seems": 2,
            "doable": 1,
            "kramer": 3,
            "recommend": 1,
            "two": 1,
            "yesterday": 1,
            "2": 1,
            "hour": 2,
            "back": 1,
            "relatively": 1,
            "fit": 1,
            "consider": 1,
            "beginner": 1,
            "rocky": 1,
            "path": 1,
            "across": 1,
            "stressing": 1,
            "another": 1,
            "hike": 1,
            "leave": 1,
            "munich": 1,
            "local": 1,
            "seen": 1,
            "leisurely": 1,
            "part": 1,
            "nicest": 1,
            "option": 1,
            "though": 1,
            "intriguing": 1,
            "intimidating": 1,
            "bad": 1,
            "idea": 1,
            "level": 1,
            "stick": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Positive",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Herzogstand",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Wank",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Kramer",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "two",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Herzogstand",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "yesterday",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "about 2 hours",
                "label": "TIME"
            },
            {
                "text": "about an hour",
                "label": "TIME"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Wank",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Kramer",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Wank",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t4qrga": {
        "id": "t3_1t4qrga",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T20:04:38.001Z",
        "title": "Romantic restaurant to celebrate wedding anniversary",
        "body": "Hi all,\n\nWe’re looking for some nice restaurant recommendations to celebrate our first wedding anniversary 😊\n\nWe’ll be traveling from Ingolstadt, so anything in or around the area works. Ideally, we’re looking for a romantic spot or somewhere that offers a candlelight dinner vibe.\n\nNote: One of us is vegetarian, so good veg options would be really appreciated!\n\nThanks in advance 🙏",
        "keywords": {
            "romantic": 2,
            "restaurant": 2,
            "celebrate": 2,
            "wedding": 2,
            "anniversary": 2,
            "hi": 1,
            "looking": 2,
            "nice": 1,
            "recommendation": 1,
            "first": 1,
            "traveling": 1,
            "ingolstadt": 1,
            "anything": 1,
            "around": 1,
            "area": 1,
            "work": 1,
            "ideally": 1,
            "spot": 1,
            "somewhere": 1,
            "offer": 1,
            "candlelight": 1,
            "dinner": 1,
            "vibe": 1,
            "note": 1,
            "one": 1,
            "vegetarian": 1,
            "good": 1,
            "veg": 1,
            "option": 1,
            "appreciated": 1,
            "thanks": 1,
            "advance": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Positive",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "first",
                "label": "ORDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Ingolstadt",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "One",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "🙏",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t4ruzc": {
        "id": "t3_1t4ruzc",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T20:43:59.635Z",
        "title": "Maybe, was at our door!",
        "body": "",
        "keywords": {
            "door": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": []
    },
    "t3_1t4p42k": {
        "id": "t3_1t4p42k",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T19:06:04.322Z",
        "title": "Mercedes Repair Shop suggestion",
        "body": "Hi all,\n\nim looking for a mercedes free repair shop around Munich preferably at north, since 10 years I visit original but for me it does not make sense anymore except service intervals.\n\nI dont like the atu etc, need a master explicitly for mercedes.\n\nthanks in advance.",
        "keywords": {
            "mercedes": 3,
            "repair": 2,
            "shop": 2,
            "suggestion": 1,
            "hi": 1,
            "im": 1,
            "looking": 1,
            "free": 1,
            "around": 1,
            "munich": 1,
            "preferably": 1,
            "north": 1,
            "since": 1,
            "10": 1,
            "year": 1,
            "visit": 1,
            "original": 1,
            "sense": 1,
            "anymore": 1,
            "except": 1,
            "service": 1,
            "interval": 1,
            "dont": 1,
            "atu": 1,
            "etc": 1,
            "need": 1,
            "master": 1,
            "explicitly": 1,
            "thanks": 1,
            "advance": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Mercedes Repair Shop",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "10 years",
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t4fhgl": {
        "id": "t3_1t4fhgl",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T13:27:47.062Z",
        "title": "Best time and place to buy a proper pair of Lederhosen",
        "body": "Hi everyone! I want to get an authentic Lederhosen for the next Oktoberfest. Do you have any recommendations on when and where I should shop to find the best prices?",
        "keywords": {
            "best": 2,
            "time": 1,
            "place": 1,
            "buy": 1,
            "proper": 1,
            "pair": 1,
            "lederhosen": 2,
            "hi": 1,
            "everyone": 1,
            "authentic": 1,
            "next": 1,
            "oktoberfest": 1,
            "recommendation": 1,
            "shop": 1,
            "find": 1,
            "price": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Positive",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Lederhosen Hi",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Lederhosen",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Oktoberfest",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t4drrs": {
        "id": "t3_1t4drrs",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T12:18:34.896Z",
        "title": "Recommendations for renting a E-Roller/Moped for the summer?",
        "body": "Hey everyone - I'd love to rent a electric motorcycle (like a Vespa or Unu) during the summer months. Do you have any recommendations of companies that does that? I tried to google it but it wasn't easy, honestly.",
        "keywords": {
            "recommendation": 2,
            "renting": 1,
            "summer": 2,
            "hey": 1,
            "everyone": 1,
            "love": 1,
            "rent": 1,
            "electric": 1,
            "motorcycle": 1,
            "vespa": 1,
            "unu": 1,
            "month": 1,
            "company": 1,
            "tried": 1,
            "google": 1,
            "easy": 1,
            "honestly": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Positive",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "E-Roller/Moped",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "the summer",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Vespa",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "the summer months",
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t4iwhj": {
        "id": "t3_1t4iwhj",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T15:32:44.378Z",
        "title": "Walking Aid / Wheelchair",
        "body": "Hello, my mother is very unwell and I’m trying to find her a second hand walking frame / zimmerframe that she can use in the house.\n\nIf there a second hand / charity shop that sells such equipment?\n\nI would also like to get her an electric wheelchair, again if anyone knows a marketplace for these I would appreciate any direction. Thank you\n\nIf this post isn’t allowed please delete.",
        "keywords": {
            "walking": 2,
            "aid": 1,
            "wheelchair": 2,
            "hello": 1,
            "mother": 1,
            "unwell": 1,
            "trying": 1,
            "find": 1,
            "second": 2,
            "hand": 2,
            "frame": 1,
            "zimmerframe": 1,
            "use": 1,
            "house": 1,
            "charity": 1,
            "shop": 1,
            "sell": 1,
            "equipment": 1,
            "electric": 1,
            "marketplace": 1,
            "appreciate": 1,
            "direction": 1,
            "thank": 1,
            "allowed": 1,
            "please": 1,
            "delete": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "second",
                "label": "ORDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "second",
                "label": "ORDINAL"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t4d459": {
        "id": "t3_1t4d459",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T11:49:35.932Z",
        "title": "Joost Klein",
        "body": "Hey i’m M/32 and\n\nDoes anyone want to come to the Joost Klein concert on June 8th? There are still tickets 🎫\nCould be Funny 🙏\n\nHat jemand Lust mit zu Joost Klein zu kommen? :)",
        "keywords": {
            "joost": 3,
            "klein": 3,
            "hey": 1,
            "come": 1,
            "concert": 1,
            "june": 1,
            "8th": 1,
            "ticket": 1,
            "funny": 1,
            "hat": 1,
            "jemand": 1,
            "lust": 1,
            "mit": 1,
            "zu": 2,
            "kommen": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Positive",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Klein",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "June 8th",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Klein",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t4c1ah": {
        "id": "t3_1t4c1ah",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T10:58:49.518Z",
        "title": "Any large open spaces or \"lost places\" that aren't too far out, but remote/desolate enough to fly an FPV drone?",
        "body": "I only have experience with regular non fpv drones (or rather goggles) and I intend to fly under \"Verbandsregeln\", allowing for limited fpv drone piloting in the open without a spotter.\n\nI usually start my regular drone in an area where nobody is disturbed and then keep it at a height that people only know there's a drone because I have a controller in my hands.\n\nWith an FPV drone, you want to fly close to obstacles, get some cool action shots, not panoramic views - so where can I safely test that? Of course asking a farmer a bit further out is a possibility, but a bit boring. Something like a \"lost place\" that nobody cares about would be perfect, alternatively some field with more than just some grass and small bushes that a drone won't fit through.\n\nDoes anyone have ideas, or even experience?\n\nThe picture is purely to generate clicks and is taken on a normal stabilised drone with screen/controller combo, and has nothing to do with fpv :)",
        "keywords": {
            "large": 1,
            "open": 2,
            "space": 1,
            "lost": 2,
            "place": 2,
            "far": 1,
            "enough": 1,
            "fly": 3,
            "fpv": 5,
            "drone": 8,
            "experience": 2,
            "regular": 2,
            "non": 1,
            "rather": 1,
            "goggles": 1,
            "intend": 1,
            "verbandsregeln": 1,
            "allowing": 1,
            "limited": 1,
            "piloting": 1,
            "without": 1,
            "spotter": 1,
            "usually": 1,
            "start": 1,
            "area": 1,
            "nobody": 2,
            "disturbed": 1,
            "keep": 1,
            "height": 1,
            "people": 1,
            "controller": 1,
            "hand": 1,
            "close": 1,
            "obstacle": 1,
            "cool": 1,
            "action": 1,
            "shot": 1,
            "panoramic": 1,
            "view": 1,
            "safely": 1,
            "test": 1,
            "course": 1,
            "asking": 1,
            "farmer": 1,
            "bit": 2,
            "possibility": 1,
            "boring": 1,
            "something": 1,
            "care": 1,
            "perfect": 1,
            "alternatively": 1,
            "field": 1,
            "grass": 1,
            "small": 1,
            "bush": 1,
            "wo": 1,
            "fit": 1,
            "idea": 1,
            "picture": 1,
            "purely": 1,
            "generate": 1,
            "click": 1,
            "normal": 1,
            "stabilised": 1,
            "combo": 1,
            "nothing": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "FPV",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Verbandsregeln",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
            },
            {
                "text": "FPV",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t4a9uh": {
        "id": "t3_1t4a9uh",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T09:24:12.616Z",
        "title": "Englischer Garten / Monowiese Starterpack",
        "body": "",
        "keywords": {
            "englischer": 1,
            "garten": 1,
            "monowiese": 1,
            "starterpack": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Englischer Garten",
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t48vzn": {
        "id": "t3_1t48vzn",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T08:00:56.166Z",
        "title": "Frühlingsfest at daylight and night",
        "body": "https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LtQx15mfRQE\n\nHey guys I hope you enjoy these fotos of the Frühlingsfest.\nThese are some frames from a short video I made about it.\nI hope you enjoy them",
        "keywords": {
            "frühlingsfest": 2,
            "daylight": 1,
            "night": 1,
            "hey": 1,
            "guy": 1,
            "hope": 2,
            "enjoy": 2,
            "fotos": 1,
            "frame": 1,
            "short": 1,
            "video": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Positive",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "daylight and night https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LtQx15mfRQE",
                "label": "TIME"
            },
            {
                "text": "Frühlingsfest",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t4hgpa": {
        "id": "t3_1t4hgpa",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T14:41:16.669Z",
        "title": "If you only fly out of T2, T1 is quiet the disappointment",
        "body": "No liquids +100ml >:(, too little shopping options, no electricity sockets at gates, dated buildings. When landing, not enough signs to direct you to the trains/SEV.",
        "keywords": {
            "fly": 1,
            "t2": 1,
            "t1": 1,
            "quiet": 1,
            "disappointment": 1,
            "liquid": 1,
            "little": 1,
            "shopping": 1,
            "option": 1,
            "electricity": 1,
            "socket": 1,
            "gate": 1,
            "dated": 1,
            "building": 1,
            "landing": 1,
            "enough": 1,
            "sign": 1,
            "direct": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "T2",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "T1",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "SEV",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t3ua2r": {
        "id": "t3_1t3ua2r",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-04T20:49:53.015Z",
        "title": "Anyone in Munich wanna start a punk band?",
        "body": "I’m trying to put together a punk band here in Munich. Think raw energy, DIY attitude, and not overproduced.\n\nanyone wanna join?",
        "keywords": {
            "munich": 2,
            "wan": 2,
            "na": 2,
            "start": 1,
            "punk": 2,
            "band": 2,
            "trying": 1,
            "put": 1,
            "together": 1,
            "think": 1,
            "raw": 1,
            "energy": 1,
            "diy": 1,
            "attitude": 1,
            "overproduced": 1,
            "join": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "DIY",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t3wg30": {
        "id": "t3_1t3wg30",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-04T22:10:27.945Z",
        "title": "Tickets zu verschenken",
        "body": "4 Tickets für FCB Frauen gegen TSG 1899 Hoffenheim am 06.05. um 18 Uhr zu verschenken.\n\nHab sie selbst geschenkt bekommen und es war lange nicht klar, wann das Spiel stattfindet. Leider können wir am Mittwoch nicht. Würde sie gerne weiter verschenken an jemanden, der Interesse hat 😊",
        "keywords": {
            "ticket": 2,
            "zu": 2,
            "verschenken": 3,
            "4": 1,
            "für": 1,
            "fcb": 1,
            "frau": 1,
            "gegen": 1,
            "tsg": 1,
            "1899": 1,
            "hoffenheim": 1,
            "um": 1,
            "18": 1,
            "uhr": 1,
            "hab": 1,
            "sie": 2,
            "selbst": 1,
            "geschenkt": 1,
            "bekommen": 1,
            "und": 1,
            "e": 1,
            "war": 1,
            "lange": 1,
            "nicht": 2,
            "klar": 1,
            "wann": 1,
            "da": 1,
            "spiel": 1,
            "stattfindet": 1,
            "leider": 1,
            "können": 1,
            "wir": 1,
            "mittwoch": 1,
            "würde": 1,
            "gerne": 1,
            "weiter": 1,
            "jemanden": 1,
            "der": 1,
            "interesse": 1,
            "hat": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "4",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "FCB Frauen gegen",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "1899",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Hoffenheim",
                "label": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "text": "06.05",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "18",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "das Spiel",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Leider können",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Würde",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "weiter verschenken",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "jemanden",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Interesse",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t3sb9m": {
        "id": "t3_1t3sb9m",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-04T19:40:36.880Z",
        "title": "Lost my external SSD",
        "body": "Hello everyone!\n\nLast friday I lost an external SSD of 1TB with tons of videos of my fitness progress, plus a couple travel videos🥲. Honestly I don't know where I lost it... I was at the calisthenics park by the Isar (Entenweiher) and I had it in my backpack, but I don't know if it fell off my bike on the way home...\n\nIt's a grey magnetic USB-C SSD. I am willing to discuss a reward cause the videos really mean a lot to me.\n\nI already reported the loss at the Fundbüro, but thought it wouldn't hurt to post it here too.\n\nThanks and let this be a reminder of keeping a back up of your important photos and videos 🥹",
        "keywords": {
            "lost": 3,
            "external": 2,
            "ssd": 3,
            "hello": 1,
            "everyone": 1,
            "last": 1,
            "friday": 1,
            "1tb": 1,
            "ton": 1,
            "video": 3,
            "fitness": 1,
            "progress": 1,
            "plus": 1,
            "couple": 1,
            "travel": 1,
            "honestly": 1,
            "calisthenics": 1,
            "park": 1,
            "isar": 1,
            "entenweiher": 1,
            "backpack": 1,
            "fell": 1,
            "bike": 1,
            "way": 1,
            "home": 1,
            "grey": 1,
            "magnetic": 1,
            "willing": 1,
            "discus": 1,
            "reward": 1,
            "cause": 1,
            "mean": 1,
            "already": 1,
            "reported": 1,
            "loss": 1,
            "fundbüro": 1,
            "thought": 1,
            "hurt": 1,
            "thanks": 1,
            "let": 1,
            "reminder": 1,
            "keeping": 1,
            "back": 1,
            "important": 1,
            "photo": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Last friday",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "1",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Fundbüro",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t488js": {
        "id": "t3_1t488js",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-05T07:21:26.582Z",
        "title": "Aus gegebenem Anlass",
        "body": "",
        "keywords": {
            "au": 1,
            "gegebenem": 1,
            "anlass": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": []
    },
    "t3_1t3j9ht": {
        "id": "t3_1t3j9ht",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-04T14:25:39.586Z",
        "title": "No ADHS/Psychiatry appointments from 15+ doctors?",
        "body": "Is it normal that we (me, my doctor, and my workplace colleague from HR) can't find a doctor that will accept a new patient? My workplace colleague even quit and now we are with even less help.\n\nThis is getting \"criminally\" bad that no one will accept us, some even close the phone on my face sometimes (so much for mental help centers). I even got an official diagnosis from another country (with official lawyer translations and stamps) just to justify that I have ADHS and a doctor's response was \"I only treat people with my own diagnosis, I won't accept from others, even if it was from Germany.\" .\n\nWhat makes it bad is that they don't even offer appointment in let's say 5-6 months but they flat out say \"no new patients\".\n\nThe problem is I cant travel outside Germany every month or other month to get prescription and pay private for meds and counselling. It's not just the cost but I tend to get sick about 1/3 times I fly, with whatever virus people carry each time on the flight. I have TK insurance just in case this helps with suggestions.\n\nSome of them refuse because they don't speak English but the response is \"Keine Terminvereinbarung für neue Patienten\" so even if I try to communicate a bit, it makes no change.",
        "keywords": {
            "appointment": 2,
            "doctor": 4,
            "normal": 1,
            "workplace": 2,
            "colleague": 2,
            "hr": 1,
            "ca": 1,
            "find": 1,
            "accept": 3,
            "new": 2,
            "patient": 2,
            "quit": 1,
            "less": 1,
            "help": 3,
            "criminally": 1,
            "bad": 2,
            "one": 1,
            "close": 1,
            "phone": 1,
            "face": 1,
            "sometimes": 1,
            "mental": 1,
            "center": 1,
            "official": 2,
            "diagnosis": 2,
            "another": 1,
            "country": 1,
            "lawyer": 1,
            "translation": 1,
            "stamp": 1,
            "justify": 1,
            "adh": 1,
            "response": 2,
            "treat": 1,
            "people": 2,
            "wo": 1,
            "others": 1,
            "germany": 2,
            "make": 2,
            "offer": 1,
            "let": 1,
            "say": 2,
            "month": 3,
            "flat": 1,
            "problem": 1,
            "cant": 1,
            "travel": 1,
            "outside": 1,
            "every": 1,
            "prescription": 1,
            "pay": 1,
            "private": 1,
            "med": 1,
            "counselling": 1,
            "cost": 1,
            "tend": 1,
            "sick": 1,
            "time": 2,
            "fly": 1,
            "whatever": 1,
            "virus": 1,
            "carry": 1,
            "flight": 1,
            "tk": 1,
            "insurance": 1,
            "case": 1,
            "suggestion": 1,
            "refuse": 1,
            "speak": 1,
            "english": 1,
            "keine": 1,
            "terminvereinbarung": 1,
            "für": 1,
            "neue": 1,
            "patienten": 1,
            "try": 1,
            "communicate": 1,
            "bit": 1,
            "change": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "15+",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Germany",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "5-6 months",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Germany",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "about 1/3",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "English",
                "label": "LANGUAGE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Keine Terminvereinbarung",
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t3hw4i": {
        "id": "t3_1t3hw4i",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-04T13:34:29.784Z",
        "title": "Looking for friends in Dachau!",
        "body": "Hi!\n\nI'm looking for friends in/near Dachau/Karlsfeld.\n\nWould love to find people to go Boulder at Naturfreundehalle Dachau, swimming, play cardgames with, go to \"Jazz in allen Gassen\"....\n\nPreferably German speaking between 25 and 35! No dating ;)\n\nWould love to meet y'all!\n\n- a 28 year old women who recently moved here",
        "keywords": {
            "looking": 2,
            "friend": 2,
            "dachau": 2,
            "hi": 1,
            "love": 2,
            "find": 1,
            "people": 1,
            "boulder": 1,
            "naturfreundehalle": 1,
            "swimming": 1,
            "play": 1,
            "cardgames": 1,
            "jazz": 1,
            "allen": 1,
            "gassen": 1,
            "preferably": 1,
            "german": 1,
            "speaking": 1,
            "25": 1,
            "35": 1,
            "dating": 1,
            "meet": 1,
            "28": 1,
            "year": 1,
            "old": 1,
            "woman": 1,
            "recently": 1,
            "moved": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Positive",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Dachau",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Dachau",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Boulder",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Naturfreundehalle Dachau",
                "label": "FAC"
            },
            {
                "text": "Gassen",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "German",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "between 25 and 35",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "28 year old",
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t3gkkc": {
        "id": "t3_1t3gkkc",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-04T12:42:09.897Z",
        "title": "S3- Sauerlach - Giesing/ Samstag 02.Mai - Missed connection! zufällige Begegnung",
        "body": "Saturday evening S3 (Sauerlach → Giesing) – missed connection 🚲\n\nThis is a bit of a long shot, but worth trying.\n\nOn Saturday around 19:24, I got on the S3 from Sauerlach with my kids and our bikes. You were already on the train with your bike (you must have boarded earlier, likely from Otterfing or Holzkirchen). You were doing Sudoku, and you seemed a bit amused by whatever the kids were up to 🙂\n\nYou got off at Giesing.\n\nIf this happens to reach you and you’d be open to it, I’d enjoy grabbing a coffee sometime 🙂\n\nAnd if this sounds familiar to someone who knows her, feel free to pass it along.\n\n \n\n \n\nSamstagabend S3 (Sauerlach → Giesing) – dich gesehen, nicht angesprochen 🚲\n\nIst ein ziemlicher Long Shot, aber ich probier’s einfach mal.\n\nAm Samstag gegen 19:24 bin ich mit meinen Kindern und unseren Fahrrädern in Sauerlach in die S3 gestiegen. Du warst schon im Zug mit deinem Rad (vermutlich bist du vorher eingestiegen, vielleicht in Otterfing oder Holzkirchen). Du hast Sudoku gemacht, und es wirkte, als ob dich das, was die Kinder gemacht haben, ein bisschen amüsiert hat 🙂\n\nDu bist in Giesing ausgestiegen.\n\nFalls du das hier zufällig siehst und Lust hast: Ich würde mich freuen, mal zusammen einen Kaffee trinken zu gehen 🙂\n\nUnd falls jemand meint, die Person zu kennen – gerne weiterleiten.",
        "keywords": {
            "sauerlach": 5,
            "samstag": 2,
            "missed": 2,
            "connection": 2,
            "zufällige": 1,
            "begegnung": 1,
            "saturday": 2,
            "evening": 1,
            "s3": 4,
            "giesing": 4,
            "bit": 2,
            "long": 2,
            "shot": 2,
            "worth": 1,
            "trying": 1,
            "around": 1,
            "kid": 2,
            "bike": 2,
            "already": 1,
            "train": 1,
            "boarded": 1,
            "earlier": 1,
            "likely": 1,
            "otterfing": 2,
            "holzkirchen": 2,
            "sudoku": 2,
            "seemed": 1,
            "amused": 1,
            "whatever": 1,
            "happens": 1,
            "reach": 1,
            "open": 1,
            "enjoy": 1,
            "grabbing": 1,
            "coffee": 1,
            "sometime": 1,
            "sound": 1,
            "familiar": 1,
            "feel": 1,
            "free": 1,
            "pas": 1,
            "along": 1,
            "samstagabend": 1,
            "dich": 2,
            "gesehen": 1,
            "nicht": 1,
            "angesprochen": 1,
            "ist": 1,
            "ein": 2,
            "ziemlicher": 1,
            "aber": 1,
            "ich": 3,
            "probier": 1,
            "einfach": 1,
            "mal": 2,
            "gegen": 1,
            "bin": 1,
            "mit": 2,
            "meinen": 1,
            "kindern": 1,
            "und": 4,
            "unseren": 1,
            "fahrrädern": 1,
            "die": 3,
            "gestiegen": 1,
            "du": 5,
            "warst": 1,
            "schon": 1,
            "im": 1,
            "zug": 1,
            "deinem": 1,
            "rad": 1,
            "vermutlich": 1,
            "bist": 2,
            "vorher": 1,
            "eingestiegen": 1,
            "vielleicht": 1,
            "oder": 1,
            "hast": 2,
            "gemacht": 2,
            "e": 1,
            "wirkte": 1,
            "al": 1,
            "ob": 1,
            "da": 2,
            "kinder": 1,
            "haben": 1,
            "bisschen": 1,
            "amüsiert": 1,
            "hat": 1,
            "ausgestiegen": 1,
            "fall": 2,
            "hier": 1,
            "zufällig": 1,
            "siehst": 1,
            "lust": 1,
            "würde": 1,
            "mich": 1,
            "freuen": 1,
            "zusammen": 1,
            "einen": 1,
            "kaffee": 1,
            "trinken": 1,
            "zu": 2,
            "gehen": 1,
            "jemand": 1,
            "meint": 1,
            "person": 1,
            "kennen": 1,
            "gerne": 1,
            "weiterleiten": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "02.Mai",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Begegnung",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Saturday evening",
                "label": "TIME"
            },
            {
                "text": "S3",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Giesing",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Saturday",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "S3",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Otterfing or Holzkirchen",
                "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
            },
            {
                "text": "Sudoku",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Giesing",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Giesing",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "🚲\n\nIst",
                "label": "PRODUCT"
            },
            {
                "text": "Long Shot",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "19:24 bin ich mit",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Fahrrädern",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "S3",
                "label": "PRODUCT"
            },
            {
                "text": "Zug",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "deinem Rad",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Kinder",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "ein bisschen",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "amüsiert hat 🙂",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Giesing",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "das",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Lust",
                "label": "PRODUCT"
            },
            {
                "text": "Kaffee",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t3j6n9": {
        "id": "t3_1t3j6n9",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-04T14:22:52.793Z",
        "title": "Offroad Motorradstrecken um München",
        "body": "Servus an die Motorradfahrer!\n\nGibt’s um München Möglichkeiten, mit dem Motorrad abseits der Wege zu fahren?\n\nGrüße",
        "keywords": {
            "offroad": 1,
            "motorradstrecken": 1,
            "um": 2,
            "münchen": 2,
            "servus": 1,
            "die": 1,
            "motorradfahrer": 1,
            "gibt": 1,
            "möglichkeiten": 1,
            "mit": 1,
            "dem": 1,
            "motorrad": 1,
            "abseits": 1,
            "der": 1,
            "wege": 1,
            "zu": 1,
            "fahren": 1,
            "grüße": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Offroad Motorradstrecken",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Servus",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Motorradfahrer",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Gibt",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "München Möglichkeiten",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "mit dem Motorrad",
                "label": "PERSON"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t3cgat": {
        "id": "t3_1t3cgat",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-04T09:16:24.546Z",
        "title": "Elektro - Photo Flohmarkt",
        "body": "Hallo zusammen, gibt es den in München Flohmärkte wo man vermehr alles rund um analoge Fotografie finden könnte?",
        "keywords": {
            "elektro": 1,
            "photo": 1,
            "flohmarkt": 1,
            "hallo": 1,
            "zusammen": 1,
            "gibt": 1,
            "e": 1,
            "den": 1,
            "münchen": 1,
            "flohmärkte": 1,
            "wo": 1,
            "man": 1,
            "vermehr": 1,
            "alles": 1,
            "rund": 1,
            "um": 1,
            "analoge": 1,
            "fotografie": 1,
            "finden": 1,
            "könnte": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Elektro - Photo Flohmarkt Hallo",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "München",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Fotografie",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t3q9am": {
        "id": "t3_1t3q9am",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-04T18:29:27.961Z",
        "title": "Leftist/less status driven community in Munich",
        "body": "I am looking for places where people with a more down to earth and social mindset meet up. This can probably be anywhere since Munich is politically not as conservative as the rest of Bavaria, but I was just wondering where to hang out where people talk less about money and status. It does not necessarily have to be political talk, but generally well-read people with a more social approach, if that makes sense.",
        "keywords": {
            "status": 2,
            "driven": 1,
            "community": 1,
            "munich": 2,
            "looking": 1,
            "place": 1,
            "people": 3,
            "earth": 1,
            "social": 2,
            "mindset": 1,
            "meet": 1,
            "anywhere": 1,
            "since": 1,
            "politically": 1,
            "conservative": 1,
            "rest": 1,
            "bavaria": 1,
            "wondering": 1,
            "hang": 1,
            "talk": 2,
            "less": 1,
            "money": 1,
            "necessarily": 1,
            "political": 1,
            "generally": 1,
            "approach": 1,
            "make": 1,
            "sense": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Bavaria",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t2xhtg": {
        "id": "t3_1t2xhtg",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-03T21:03:10.138Z",
        "title": "Public pianos in Garching / TUM campus?",
        "body": "Hi everyone!\n\nI'll be in Garching for a couple of days for a job interview, and I was wondering if there are any public pianos around the TUM campus or nearby.\n\nI read somewhere that there might be one in the mathematics department building, does anyone know if it's still there or accessible?\n\nWould be really nice to find a place to play a bit and relax before the interview 🙂\nThanks in advance!",
        "keywords": {
            "public": 2,
            "piano": 2,
            "garching": 2,
            "tum": 2,
            "campus": 2,
            "hi": 1,
            "everyone": 1,
            "couple": 1,
            "day": 1,
            "job": 1,
            "interview": 2,
            "wondering": 1,
            "around": 1,
            "nearby": 1,
            "read": 1,
            "somewhere": 1,
            "one": 1,
            "mathematics": 1,
            "department": 1,
            "building": 1,
            "accessible": 1,
            "nice": 1,
            "find": 1,
            "place": 1,
            "play": 1,
            "bit": 1,
            "relax": 1,
            "thanks": 1,
            "advance": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Positive",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Garching",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Garching",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "a couple of days",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "TUM",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t39qd5": {
        "id": "t3_1t39qd5",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-04T06:34:09.945Z",
        "title": "Preise Body&Soul",
        "body": "Kennt eventuell jemand die aktuellen Preise von Body&Soul in München? Eventuell sogar ob es einen Studentenrabatt gibt?\nWäre eine große Hilfe, online findet man ja absolut keine Infos.",
        "keywords": {
            "preise": 2,
            "body": 2,
            "soul": 2,
            "kennt": 1,
            "eventuell": 2,
            "jemand": 1,
            "die": 1,
            "aktuellen": 1,
            "von": 1,
            "münchen": 1,
            "sogar": 1,
            "ob": 1,
            "e": 1,
            "einen": 1,
            "studentenrabatt": 1,
            "gibt": 1,
            "wäre": 1,
            "eine": 1,
            "große": 1,
            "hilfe": 1,
            "online": 1,
            "findet": 1,
            "man": 1,
            "ja": 1,
            "absolut": 1,
            "keine": 1,
            "info": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Kennt eventuell",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Preise von Body&Soul",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "München",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Eventuell",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Studentenrabatt",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Wäre",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Hilfe",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "ja absolut keine",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Infos",
                "label": "ORG"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t3c5iy": {
        "id": "t3_1t3c5iy",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-04T08:59:25.323Z",
        "title": "Looking for foodie friends",
        "body": "Hi everyone! I hope this message is appropriate for this group.\n\nMy name is Natalia, I am 39F, I have been living in Munich for 10 years. I totally love it here=). I have recently developed a passion for trying out different foods (especially sweet stuff=) ), but I am a sportsman, and somehow I don't really have any foodie friends - and it's just so much more fun to try out cafes with someone and not alone, it lets you exchange opinions and share foods, so that you can try more different things!\n\nWould anyone be interested in trying out some restaurants or cafes with me? Or maybe someone can recommend me where I can find foodie friends=)? For example, one of my passions is mousse cakes (entremets), but these are rare in Munich, and I can very rarely find someone to go to such a cafe with me.\n\nWishing everyone a nice day in any case^_^",
        "keywords": {
            "looking": 1,
            "foodie": 3,
            "friend": 2,
            "hi": 1,
            "everyone": 2,
            "hope": 1,
            "message": 1,
            "appropriate": 1,
            "group": 1,
            "name": 1,
            "natalia": 1,
            "39f": 1,
            "living": 1,
            "munich": 2,
            "10": 1,
            "year": 1,
            "totally": 1,
            "love": 1,
            "recently": 1,
            "developed": 1,
            "passion": 2,
            "trying": 2,
            "different": 2,
            "food": 2,
            "especially": 1,
            "sweet": 1,
            "sportsman": 1,
            "somehow": 1,
            "fun": 1,
            "try": 2,
            "cafe": 3,
            "alone": 1,
            "let": 1,
            "exchange": 1,
            "opinion": 1,
            "share": 1,
            "interested": 1,
            "restaurant": 1,
            "recommend": 1,
            "find": 2,
            "example": 1,
            "one": 1,
            "mousse": 1,
            "cake": 1,
            "entremets": 1,
            "rare": 1,
            "rarely": 1,
            "wishing": 1,
            "nice": 1,
            "day": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Positive",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Natalia",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "10 years",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "one",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "a nice day",
                "label": "DATE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t2wjyo": {
        "id": "t3_1t2wjyo",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-03T20:27:26.014Z",
        "title": "Need a local kitchen planner in Munich (IKEA service not working)",
        "body": "I’m moving into a new apartment near Münchner Freiheit (Schwabing) and, as is typical here, it doesn’t come with a kitchen. I need to get one fitted myself and was planning to buy from IKEA.\n\nThe catch: my landlord doesn’t have a kitchen plan for the unit, so I don’t have documentation on where the water supply, drainage, or electrical sockets are. Honestly, I don’t trust myself to figure this out and measure it correctly on my own, so I really need external help here. I’d want someone to come measure the space, document the existing connections, and put together a proper plan I can then use to design the kitchen on the IKEA website.\n\nI tried booking the IKEA kitchen planning service, but their site keeps telling me it’s not available in my location, and I haven’t been able to book a call either. So I’m looking for a local alternative in Munich, basically an independent kitchen planner or a handyman/Schreiner who can produce a measured drawing with the connection points marked.\n\nDoes anyone have a recommendation? Bonus if they speak English",
        "keywords": {
            "need": 3,
            "local": 2,
            "kitchen": 6,
            "planner": 2,
            "munich": 2,
            "ikea": 4,
            "service": 2,
            "working": 1,
            "moving": 1,
            "new": 1,
            "apartment": 1,
            "near": 1,
            "münchner": 1,
            "freiheit": 1,
            "schwabing": 1,
            "typical": 1,
            "come": 2,
            "one": 1,
            "fitted": 1,
            "planning": 2,
            "buy": 1,
            "catch": 1,
            "landlord": 1,
            "plan": 2,
            "unit": 1,
            "documentation": 1,
            "water": 1,
            "supply": 1,
            "drainage": 1,
            "electrical": 1,
            "socket": 1,
            "honestly": 1,
            "trust": 1,
            "figure": 1,
            "measure": 2,
            "correctly": 1,
            "external": 1,
            "help": 1,
            "space": 1,
            "document": 1,
            "existing": 1,
            "connection": 2,
            "put": 1,
            "together": 1,
            "proper": 1,
            "use": 1,
            "design": 1,
            "website": 1,
            "tried": 1,
            "booking": 1,
            "site": 1,
            "keep": 1,
            "telling": 1,
            "available": 1,
            "location": 1,
            "able": 1,
            "book": 1,
            "call": 1,
            "either": 1,
            "looking": 1,
            "alternative": 1,
            "independent": 1,
            "produce": 1,
            "measured": 1,
            "drawing": 1,
            "point": 1,
            "marked": 1,
            "recommendation": 1,
            "bonus": 1,
            "speak": 1,
            "english": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "IKEA",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Münchner Freiheit",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "one",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "IKEA",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "n’t",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "IKEA",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "IKEA",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "English",
                "label": "LANGUAGE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t2wnm7": {
        "id": "t3_1t2wnm7",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-03T20:31:15.746Z",
        "title": "Any chance of finding any rent cheaper than 800-900 near Munich including utilities?",
        "body": "Now i rent an apartment in Bad Aibling(near Rosenheim) for only 330€ a month, but long story short im gonna get kicked out in the near future.\n\nI'm fine with a 30-40min commute by car and i don't care if the city/village has good public transportation.\n\nAlso i don't need anything fancy, all i need is one bedroom, a batroom and a kitchen and im all set.\n\nThink i have any chance of finding something cheaper than 800?",
        "keywords": {
            "chance": 2,
            "finding": 2,
            "rent": 2,
            "cheaper": 2,
            "near": 3,
            "munich": 1,
            "including": 1,
            "utility": 1,
            "apartment": 1,
            "bad": 1,
            "aibling": 1,
            "rosenheim": 1,
            "month": 1,
            "long": 1,
            "story": 1,
            "short": 1,
            "im": 2,
            "gon": 1,
            "na": 1,
            "kicked": 1,
            "future": 1,
            "fine": 1,
            "commute": 1,
            "car": 1,
            "care": 1,
            "good": 1,
            "public": 1,
            "transportation": 1,
            "need": 2,
            "anything": 1,
            "fancy": 1,
            "one": 1,
            "bedroom": 1,
            "batroom": 1,
            "kitchen": 1,
            "set": 1,
            "think": 1,
            "something": 1,
            "800": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Negative",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Bad Aibling(near Rosenheim",
                "label": "FAC"
            },
            {
                "text": "only 330€",
                "label": "MONEY"
            },
            {
                "text": "30",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            },
            {
                "text": "one",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t2v5rh": {
        "id": "t3_1t2v5rh",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-03T19:35:01.104Z",
        "title": "Wo in München kann man gut lernen?",
        "body": "Ich brauche ein bisschen Abwechslung vom Platz wo ich lerne (Abschlussprüfungen Realschule). Ich wollte am Dienstag vielleicht mit einer Freundin in eine Stadtbib gehen, aber wo kann man ansonsten noch hin? Sollte halbwegs ruhig sein, kann aber auch irgendwo in der Natur sein (an der Isar oder so). Am besten kostenlos und irgendwo wo ich unter 18 erwünscht bin.",
        "keywords": {
            "wo": 4,
            "münchen": 1,
            "kann": 3,
            "man": 2,
            "gut": 1,
            "lernen": 1,
            "ich": 4,
            "brauche": 1,
            "ein": 1,
            "bisschen": 1,
            "abwechslung": 1,
            "vom": 1,
            "platz": 1,
            "lerne": 1,
            "abschlussprüfungen": 1,
            "realschule": 1,
            "wollte": 1,
            "dienstag": 1,
            "vielleicht": 1,
            "mit": 1,
            "einer": 1,
            "freundin": 1,
            "eine": 1,
            "stadtbib": 1,
            "gehen": 1,
            "aber": 2,
            "ansonsten": 1,
            "noch": 1,
            "hin": 1,
            "sollte": 1,
            "halbwegs": 1,
            "ruhig": 1,
            "sein": 2,
            "auch": 1,
            "irgendwo": 2,
            "der": 2,
            "natur": 1,
            "isar": 1,
            "oder": 1,
            "besten": 1,
            "kostenlos": 1,
            "und": 1,
            "unter": 1,
            "18": 1,
            "erwünscht": 1,
            "bin": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "München",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "gut lernen",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Abwechslung vom Platz",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Abschlussprüfungen Realschule",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Dienstag vielleicht",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Freundin",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Stadtbib",
                "label": "LOC"
            },
            {
                "text": "wo kann",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "kann aber",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Natur",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Isar",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "18",
                "label": "CARDINAL"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t2sduu": {
        "id": "t3_1t2sduu",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-03T17:53:08.696Z",
        "title": "Looking for TK‑covered skin cancer screening in Munich",
        "body": "Hi everyone,\nI’m insured with Techniker Krankenkasse (TK) and would like to get a statutory skin‑cancer screening (Hautkrebsvorsorge) that’s fully covered by public insurance. However, I can’t seem to find any dermatologist in Munich who explicitly says they accept TK and bill the standard subsidized screening (not private/self‑pay).\n• Can anyone recommend a Hautarzt or Hausarzt in Munich who does TK‑covered skin‑cancer screening?\n• Or could you explain how to identify one in the TK‑Ärzteführer (doctor search) so I don’t accidentally book a private‑pay check‑up?\nThanks in advance!",
        "keywords": {
            "looking": 1,
            "skin": 1,
            "cancer": 1,
            "screening": 4,
            "munich": 3,
            "hi": 1,
            "everyone": 1,
            "insured": 1,
            "techniker": 1,
            "krankenkasse": 1,
            "tk": 2,
            "statutory": 1,
            "hautkrebsvorsorge": 1,
            "fully": 1,
            "covered": 1,
            "public": 1,
            "insurance": 1,
            "however": 1,
            "seem": 1,
            "find": 1,
            "dermatologist": 1,
            "explicitly": 1,
            "say": 1,
            "accept": 1,
            "bill": 1,
            "standard": 1,
            "subsidized": 1,
            "recommend": 1,
            "hautarzt": 1,
            "hausarzt": 1,
            "explain": 1,
            "identify": 1,
            "one": 1,
            "doctor": 1,
            "search": 1,
            "accidentally": 1,
            "book": 1,
            "thanks": 1,
            "advance": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Techniker Krankenkasse",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Hautkrebsvorsorge",
                "label": "PERSON"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "TK",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Hautarzt",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Hausarzt",
                "label": "ORG"
            },
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            }
        ]
    },
    "t3_1t2vv92": {
        "id": "t3_1t2vv92",
        "timestamp": "2026-05-03T20:01:19.996Z",
        "title": "Please help with Mass times",
        "body": "We will be visiting Munich in a few weeks and need to attend Catholic Mass Sunday morning. We are staying near Sendlinger Tor. I typically use masstimes .org, but always check with the actual church to confirm Mass times. When using google translate for the website for St. Peter, Asam, St. Stephen, and Church of the Holy Cross, it lists \"Holy Office\" and \"Holy Mass\" for HI. Amt and HI. Messe. I've never heard of Holy Office and don't know if google is even translating it properly. If anyone can help explain the difference between HI. Amt. and HI. Messe, I would be truly grateful. I tried using the search tool, but am not having any luck.\n\nWe prefer not to attend Traditional Latin Mass. German is fine for us even though we speak very little German. We can get by using our missal.",
        "keywords": {
            "please": 1,
            "help": 2,
            "mass": 5,
            "time": 2,
            "visiting": 1,
            "munich": 1,
            "week": 1,
            "need": 1,
            "attend": 2,
            "catholic": 1,
            "sunday": 1,
            "morning": 1,
            "staying": 1,
            "near": 1,
            "sendlinger": 1,
            "tor": 1,
            "typically": 1,
            "use": 1,
            "masstimes": 1,
            "always": 1,
            "check": 1,
            "actual": 1,
            "church": 2,
            "confirm": 1,
            "using": 3,
            "google": 2,
            "translate": 1,
            "website": 1,
            "peter": 1,
            "asam": 1,
            "stephen": 1,
            "holy": 4,
            "cross": 1,
            "list": 1,
            "office": 2,
            "hi": 4,
            "amt": 2,
            "messe": 2,
            "never": 1,
            "heard": 1,
            "translating": 1,
            "properly": 1,
            "explain": 1,
            "difference": 1,
            "truly": 1,
            "grateful": 1,
            "tried": 1,
            "search": 1,
            "tool": 1,
            "luck": 1,
            "prefer": 1,
            "traditional": 1,
            "latin": 1,
            "german": 2,
            "fine": 1,
            "though": 1,
            "speak": 1,
            "little": 1,
            "missal": 1
        },
        "sentiment": "Neutral",
        "entities": [
            {
                "text": "Munich",
                "label": "GPE"
            },
            {
                "text": "a few weeks",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
                "text": "Catholic",
                "label": "NORP"
            },
            {
                "text": "Sunday",
                "label": "DATE"
            },
            {
